var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "لِآدَمَ",
        "answer": "to Adam",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "liādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَا آدَمُ",
        "answer": "And O Adam",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wayāādamu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "آدَمَ",
        "answer": "(of) Adam",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "آدَمَ",
        "answer": "(of) Adam",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "آدَمَ",
        "answer": "(of) Adam",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "آدَمَ",
        "answer": "(of) Adam",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "آدَمَ",
        "answer": "(of) Adam ",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ādama",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِبْلِيسَ",
        "answer": "Iblis",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ib'līsa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاءَنَا",
        "answer": "our forefathers",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ābāanā",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاؤُنَا",
        "answer": "our forefathers",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ābāunā",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآبَاؤُكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your forefathers",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "waābāukum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاءَنَا",
        "answer": "our forefathers",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ābāanā",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "آبَاؤُنَا",
        "answer": "(by) our forefathers",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ābāunā",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبَوَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "your parents",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "abawaykum",
        "frequency": "117",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآتِيَنَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "surely, I will come to them",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "laātiyannahum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "come to you",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "yatiyannakum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِي",
        "answer": "(will) come",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yatī",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأْتِنَا",
        "answer": "Then bring us",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "fatinā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "ائْتِنَا",
        "answer": "Bring us",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "i'tinā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَأْتُونَ",
        "answer": "Do you commit",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "atatūna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَأْتُونَ",
        "answer": "you approach",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "latatūna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَهُمْ",
        "answer": "comes to them",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "yatiyahum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَهُمْ",
        "answer": "comes to them",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "yatiyahum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأْتِ",
        "answer": "then bring",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "fati",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتُوكَ",
        "answer": "They (will) bring to you",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "yatūka",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِيَنَا",
        "answer": "you came to us",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "tatiyanā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِنَا",
        "answer": "you bring us",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "tatinā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَتَوْا",
        "answer": "Then they came",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "fa-ataw",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "tatīhim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "come to them",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "tatīhim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "comes to them",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "yatihim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "will it come to you",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "tatīkum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "you bring them",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "tatihim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَآتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "so give them",
        "pcklId": "368",
        "tlit": "faātihim",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْتُكَ",
        "answer": "I have given you",
        "pcklId": "369",
        "tlit": "ātaytuka",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُؤْتُونَ",
        "answer": "and give",
        "pcklId": "370",
        "tlit": "wayu'tūna",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We have given you",
        "pcklId": "371",
        "tlit": "ātaynākum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We gave [him]",
        "pcklId": "372",
        "tlit": "ātaynāhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَيْتَنَا",
        "answer": "You give us",
        "pcklId": "373",
        "tlit": "ātaytanā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "He gives them",
        "pcklId": "374",
        "tlit": "ātāhumā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "آتَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "He has given them",
        "pcklId": "375",
        "tlit": "ātāhumā",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْإِثْمَ",
        "answer": "and the sin",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "wal-ith'ma",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَجْرًا",
        "answer": "surely (will be) a reward",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "la-ajran",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرَ",
        "answer": "(the) reward",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ajra",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلٌ",
        "answer": "(is a fixed) term",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ajalun",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their term",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ajaluhum",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلٍ",
        "answer": "a (fixed) term",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ajalin",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their term",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ajaluhum",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحَدٍ",
        "answer": "one",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "aḥadin",
        "frequency": "85",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُذُوا",
        "answer": "Take",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "khudhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَأْخُذَكُمْ",
        "answer": "lest seizes you",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "fayakhudhakum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذَتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "So seized them",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhathumu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذَتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "Then seized them",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhathumu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "We seized",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "akhadhnā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "So We seized them",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhnāhum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخَذْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "So We seized them",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "fa-akhadhnāhum",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "We seized",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "akhadhnā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَخُذْ",
        "answer": "So take",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "fakhudh",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَخُذْهَا",
        "answer": "So take them",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "fakhudh'hā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْخُذُوا",
        "answer": "(to) take",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yakhudhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَخَذَ",
        "answer": "and seized",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "wa-akhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذَ",
        "answer": "he took (up)",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "akhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذَتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "seized them",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "akhadhathumu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَخَذْنَا",
        "answer": "and We seized",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "wa-akhadhnā",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْخُذُونَ",
        "answer": "taking",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yakhudhūna",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْخُذُوهُ",
        "answer": "they will take it",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "yakhudhūhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْخَذْ",
        "answer": "taken",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "yu'khadh",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُذُوا",
        "answer": "(We said), \"Take",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "khudhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَذَ",
        "answer": "(was) taken",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "akhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُذِ",
        "answer": "Hold",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "khudhi",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "took",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّخِذُونَ",
        "answer": "You take",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "tattakhidhūna",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّخِذُوهُ",
        "answer": "(will) they take it",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "yattakhidhūhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّخِذُوهُ",
        "answer": "they will take it",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "yattakhidhūhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّخَذَ",
        "answer": "And took",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "wa-ittakhadha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوهُ",
        "answer": "They took it (for worship)",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhūhu",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "took",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَأْخِرُونَ",
        "answer": "seek to delay",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yastakhirūna",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "concerning the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "bil-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hereafter ",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةُ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "l-ākhiratu",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "(the) last of them",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "ukh'rāhum",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأُخْرَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "to (the) last of them",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "li-ukh'rāhum",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "(We sent) their brother",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "akhāhum",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "(We sent) their brother",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "akhāhum",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "his brother",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "akhāhum",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَخَاهُ",
        "answer": "and his brother",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-akhāhu",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَخِيهِ",
        "answer": "to his brother",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "li-akhīhi",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخِيهِ",
        "answer": "his brother",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "akhīhi",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِأَخِي",
        "answer": "and my brother",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wali-akhī",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِخْوَانُهُمْ",
        "answer": "But their brothers",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wa-ikh'wānuhum",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "202"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْتَهَا",
        "answer": "its sister (nation)",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "ukh'tahā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "[when]",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذِ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "idhi",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "So when",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "But when",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "then",
        "pcklId": "406",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "and then",
        "pcklId": "407",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "408",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذًا",
        "answer": "then",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "idhan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "آذَنَ",
        "answer": "I give permission",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ādhana",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَذَّنَ",
        "answer": "Then will announce",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "fa-adhana",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأَذَّنَ",
        "answer": "declared",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ta-adhana",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "آذَانٌ",
        "answer": "(are) ears",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "ādhānun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "آذَانٌ",
        "answer": "ears",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "ādhānun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِإِذْنِ",
        "answer": "by (the) permission",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "bi-idh'ni",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤَذِّنٌ",
        "answer": "an announcer",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "mu-adhinun",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوذِينَا",
        "answer": "We have been harmed",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ūdhīnā",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْضِ",
        "answer": "(the) earth",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "(the) earth",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the land",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْضِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your land",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "arḍikum",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "(of) the land",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسِفًا",
        "answer": "and grieved",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "asifan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "آسَىٰ",
        "answer": "I grieve",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "āsā",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِصْرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their burden",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "iṣ'rahum",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْآصَالِ",
        "answer": "and (in) the evenings",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wal-āṣāli",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْفِكُونَ",
        "answer": "they (were) falsifying",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yafikūna",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكُلَا",
        "answer": "and you both eat",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "fakulā",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلُوا",
        "answer": "and eat",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "wakulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْكُلْ",
        "answer": "(to) eat",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "takul",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُوا",
        "answer": "Eat",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "kulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُلُوا",
        "answer": "and eat",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "wakulū",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "(is) but",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "but",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "630",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "631",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "632",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "633",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "634",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "635",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "636",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those (to) whom",
        "pcklId": "385",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(will be) the ones who",
        "pcklId": "386",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "of those who",
        "pcklId": "387",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "388",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) for those who",
        "pcklId": "389",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "But those who",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "But those who",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "393",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "394",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones whom",
        "pcklId": "395",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "396",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "397",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "that which",
        "pcklId": "398",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "399",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "400",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِي",
        "answer": "but which",
        "pcklId": "401",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "402",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "403",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "404",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those",
        "pcklId": "405",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "406",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": " those",
        "pcklId": "407",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "to those who",
        "pcklId": "408",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "409",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّذِي",
        "answer": "in that which",
        "pcklId": "410",
        "tlit": "bi-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّذِي",
        "answer": "in that which",
        "pcklId": "411",
        "tlit": "bi-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "412",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "413",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "414",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "415",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "416",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "[for] those who",
        "pcklId": "417",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "418",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "419",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "420",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "421",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "422",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "423",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who",
        "pcklId": "424",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who",
        "pcklId": "425",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "426",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "427",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "whom",
        "pcklId": "428",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "429",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "So those who",
        "pcklId": "430",
        "tlit": "fa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "431",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One",
        "pcklId": "432",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "433",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "434",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(that) which",
        "pcklId": "435",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "which",
        "pcklId": "436",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "437",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "438",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "for those who",
        "pcklId": "439",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "440",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(of the) one whom",
        "pcklId": "441",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "442",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "443",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "444",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "But those who",
        "pcklId": "445",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "446",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those whom",
        "pcklId": "447",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the One Who",
        "pcklId": "448",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those whom",
        "pcklId": "449",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "450",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "451",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "alīmun",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٍ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ilāhin",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٍ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ilāhin",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٍ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "ilāhin",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهٍ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ilāhin",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآلِهَتَكَ",
        "answer": "and your gods",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "waālihataka",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهًا",
        "answer": "a god",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ilāhan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِهَةٌ",
        "answer": "gods",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ālihatun",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهًا",
        "answer": "a god",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ilāhan",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1103",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "and Allah",
        "pcklId": "1104",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1105",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1106",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1107",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(from) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1108",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "with Allah",
        "pcklId": "1109",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1110",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1111",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1112",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(is) for Allah",
        "pcklId": "1113",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1114",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1115",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1116",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1117",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1118",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1119",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1120",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1121",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1122",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1123",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1124",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1125",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1126",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1127",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1128",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1129",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1130",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1131",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1132",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1133",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1134",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1135",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1136",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1137",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah ",
        "pcklId": "1138",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1139",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1140",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1141",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1142",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1143",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "from Allah",
        "pcklId": "1144",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(belongs) to Allah",
        "pcklId": "1145",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1146",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1147",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1148",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1149",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1150",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(whom) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1151",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1152",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1153",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "And for Allah",
        "pcklId": "1154",
        "tlit": "walillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1155",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1156",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1157",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1158",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1159",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1160",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "1161",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "1162",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "1163",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلَاءَ",
        "answer": "(the) Bounties",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ālāa",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلَاءَ",
        "answer": "(the) Bounties",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ālāa",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِمْ",
        "answer": "to them (Messengers)",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "ilayhim",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "And to",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "wa-ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "And to",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "wa-ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "And to",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "wa-ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "at You",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "at",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to himself",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to You",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "till",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهَا",
        "answer": "with her",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "ilayhā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "at you",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيَّ",
        "answer": "to me",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "ilayya",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْ",
        "answer": "or",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "am",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَرْتُكَ",
        "answer": "I commanded you",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "amartuka",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَرَنَا",
        "answer": "(has) ordered us",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "amaranā",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْمُرُ",
        "answer": "order",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "yamuru",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَرَ",
        "answer": "(Has been) ordered",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "amara",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْمُرُونَ",
        "answer": "(do) you instruct",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "tamurūna",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأْمُرْ",
        "answer": "and order",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wamur",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْمُرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "He commands them",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "yamuruhum",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأْمُرْ",
        "answer": "and enjoin",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wamur",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْرِهِ",
        "answer": "by His command",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "bi-amrihi",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَمْرُ",
        "answer": "and the command",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "wal-amru",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرِ",
        "answer": "(the) command",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "amri",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْرَ",
        "answer": "(over the) matter",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "amra",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّ",
        "answer": "(of) my mother",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "umma",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُمِّيَّ",
        "answer": "the unlettered",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-umiya",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُمِّيِّ",
        "answer": "the unlettered",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-umiyi",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةٍ",
        "answer": "nation",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "ummatin",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَمٍ",
        "answer": "(the) nations",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "umamin",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةٌ",
        "answer": "a nation",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "ummatun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a community",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "ummatun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَمًا",
        "answer": "(as) communities",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "umaman",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةٌ",
        "answer": "a community",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "ummatun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَمًا",
        "answer": "(as) nations",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "umaman",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a nation",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "ummatun",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِمَّا",
        "answer": "Whether",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "immā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِمَّا",
        "answer": "or Whether",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-immā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَأَمِنَ",
        "answer": "Then did feel secure",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "afa-amina",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَأَمِنَ",
        "answer": "Or felt secure",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "awa-amina",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَأَمِنُوا",
        "answer": "Then did they feel secure",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "afa-aminū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْمَنُ",
        "answer": "feel secure",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yamanu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "who believe",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you believe",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "āmantum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "āmana",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "(who has) believed",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "yu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "(have) believed",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "(had) believed",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "to believe",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "liyu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "We believe",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "You believed",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "āmantum",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنَّا",
        "answer": "we believed",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "āmannā",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنُؤْمِنَنَّ",
        "answer": "surely, we will believe",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "lanu'minanna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُوا",
        "answer": "(will) they believe",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "yu'minū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَآمَنُوا",
        "answer": "and believed",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "waāmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "they believe",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَآمِنُوا",
        "answer": "So believe",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "faāminū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُ",
        "answer": "believes",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "yu'minu",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "will they believe",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "who believe",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "who believe",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِينٌ",
        "answer": "trustworthy",
        "pcklId": "571",
        "tlit": "amīnun",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "for the believers",
        "pcklId": "701",
        "tlit": "lil'mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "702",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) believers",
        "pcklId": "703",
        "tlit": "mu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "704",
        "tlit": "mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "believers",
        "pcklId": "705",
        "tlit": "bimu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the believers",
        "pcklId": "706",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْإِنْسِ",
        "answer": "and the men",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wal-insi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْإِنْسِ",
        "answer": "and men",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wal-insi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنَاسٌ",
        "answer": "(are) people",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "unāsun",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنَاسٍ",
        "answer": "people",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "unāsin",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلَهُ",
        "answer": "and his family",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "wa-ahlahu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَهَا",
        "answer": "its people",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ahlahā",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَ",
        "answer": "people",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ahla",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلُ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ahlu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلُ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ahlu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلِهَا",
        "answer": "its people",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ahlihā",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَهَا",
        "answer": "its people",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ahlahā",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأُولَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "about the first of them",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "liūlāhum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُولَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "(the) first of them",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ūlāhum",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلُ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "awwalu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلَ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "āla",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "آلِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "āli",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْوِيلَهُ",
        "answer": "(for) its fulfillment",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "tawīlahu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْوِيلُهُ",
        "answer": "its fulfillment",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "tawīluhu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "to Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) Signs",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Signs",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِي",
        "answer": "My Verses",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "āyātī",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Verses",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "biāyātihi",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "with Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Signs",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةً",
        "answer": "a Sign",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "āyatan",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "with Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَةٍ",
        "answer": "with a Sign",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "biāyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "in (the) Signs",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "biāyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةٍ",
        "answer": "(the) sign",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "āyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتٍ",
        "answer": "(as) signs",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "āyātin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِيَ",
        "answer": "My Signs",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "āyātiya",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَةٍ",
        "answer": "sign",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "āyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "in Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Verses",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "l-āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Verses",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "āyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "[in] Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "Our Signs",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "biāyātinā",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَةٍ",
        "answer": "a Sign",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "biāyatin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِئْسَمَا",
        "answer": "Evil is what",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "bi'samā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسُنَا",
        "answer": "Our punishment",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "basunā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسُنَا",
        "answer": "Our punishment",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "basunā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسُنَا",
        "answer": "Our punishment",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "basunā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَأْسُنَا",
        "answer": "Our punishment",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "basunā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَأْسَاءِ",
        "answer": "with adversity",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "bil-basāi",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَئِيسٍ",
        "answer": "wretched",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "baīsin",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْبَجَسَتْ",
        "answer": "Then gushed forth",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fa-inbajasat",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَحْرَ",
        "answer": "the sea",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-baḥra",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَحْرِ",
        "answer": "(by) the sea",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-baḥri",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبْخَسُوا",
        "answer": "deprive",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tabkhasū",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَدَأَكُمْ",
        "answer": "He originated you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bada-akum",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَدَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "We changed",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "baddalnā",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَدَّلَ",
        "answer": "But changed",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fabaddala",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَدَتْ",
        "answer": "became apparent",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "badat",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُبْدِيَ",
        "answer": "to make apparent",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "liyub'diya",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَارَكْنَا",
        "answer": "We blessed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "bāraknā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبَارَكَ",
        "answer": "blessed",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tabāraka",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَرَكَاتٍ",
        "answer": "blessings",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "barakātin",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَسْطَةً",
        "answer": "extensively",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "baṣ'ṭatan",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُشْرًا",
        "answer": "(as) glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "bush'ran",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَشِيرٌ",
        "answer": "and a bearer of good tidings",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "wabashīrun",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) see",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(do) they see",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْصَارُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their eyes",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "abṣāruhum",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَصَائِرُ",
        "answer": "enlightenment",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "baṣāiru",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) those who see (aright)",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "mub'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْطِشُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) hold",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yabṭishūna",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَطَلَ",
        "answer": "and became futile",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wabaṭala",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَاطِلٌ",
        "answer": "and vain",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wabāṭilun",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُبْطِلُونَ",
        "answer": "the falsifiers",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-mub'ṭilūna",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَطَنَ",
        "answer": "is concealed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "baṭana",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُبْعَثُونَ",
        "answer": "they are raised up",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yub'ʿathūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعَثْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "baʿathnā",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَبْعَثَنَّ",
        "answer": "that He would surely send",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "layabʿathanna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِمْ",
        "answer": "after them",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "baʿdihim",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "and after",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِ",
        "answer": "after him",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "baʿdihi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِي",
        "answer": "after me",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "baʿdī",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهَا",
        "answer": "after that",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "baʿdihā",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهَا",
        "answer": "after that",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "baʿdihā",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِمْ",
        "answer": "after them",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "baʿdihim",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِهِمْ",
        "answer": "after them",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "baʿdihim",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "baʿda",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدَهُ",
        "answer": "after this",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "baʿdahu",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْضُكُمْ",
        "answer": "some of you",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "baʿḍukum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَعْضٍ",
        "answer": "to some others",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "libaʿḍin",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَغْتَةً",
        "answer": "suddenly",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "baghtatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَغْتَةً",
        "answer": "suddenly",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "baghtatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَبْغُونَهَا",
        "answer": "and seek in it",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wayabghūnahā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَبْغُونَهَا",
        "answer": "and seeking (to make) it",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "watabghūnahā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْغِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "I seek for you",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "abghīkum",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْبَغْيَ",
        "answer": "and the oppression",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "wal-baghya",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَلَدٍ",
        "answer": "to a land",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "libaladin",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْبَلَدُ",
        "answer": "And the land ",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wal-baladu",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُبَلِّغُكُمْ",
        "answer": "I convey to you",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "uballighukum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُبَلِّغُكُمْ",
        "answer": "I convey to you",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "uballighukum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْلَغْتُكُمْ",
        "answer": "I have conveyed to you",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "ablaghtukum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْلَغْتُكُمْ",
        "answer": "I (have) conveyed to you",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "ablaghtukum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَالِغُوهُ",
        "answer": "were to reach [it]",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "bālighūhu",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبْلُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "We test them",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nablūhum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَلَوْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "And We tested them",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wabalawnāhum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَلَاءٌ",
        "answer": "(was) a trial",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "balāon",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْنَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their sons",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "abnāahum",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْنَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your sons",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "abnāakum",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنَ",
        "answer": "O son",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ib'na",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بَنِي",
        "answer": "O Children",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "yābanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بَنِي",
        "answer": "O Children",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "yābanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بَنِي",
        "answer": "O Children",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "yābanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بَنِي",
        "answer": "O Children",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "yābanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "bibanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "(the) Children",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَوَّأَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and settled you",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wabawwa-akum",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْوَابُ",
        "answer": "(the) doors",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "abwābu",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبَابَ",
        "answer": "the gate",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-bāba",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيَاتًا",
        "answer": "(at) night",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "bayātan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيَاتًا",
        "answer": "(at) night",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bayātan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُيُوتًا",
        "answer": "(as) homes",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "buyūtan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْضَاءُ",
        "answer": "(was) white",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "bayḍāu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "among them",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَهُمَا",
        "answer": "And between them",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "wabaynahumā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "from",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَنَا",
        "answer": "between us",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "baynanā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَنَا",
        "answer": "between us",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "baynanā",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَيْنَ",
        "answer": "and between",
        "pcklId": "133",
        "tlit": "wabayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "304",
        "tlit": "bayni",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيِّنَةٌ",
        "answer": "a clear proof",
        "pcklId": "342",
        "tlit": "bayyinatun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيِّنَةٌ",
        "answer": "a clear proof",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "bayyinatun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَيِّنَاتِ",
        "answer": "with clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "bil-bayināti",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِبَيِّنَةٍ",
        "answer": "with a clear Sign",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "bibayyinatin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "open",
        "pcklId": "495",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٍ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "496",
        "tlit": "mubīnin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "manifest",
        "pcklId": "497",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "498",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَبَّرٌ",
        "answer": "destroyed",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "mutabbarun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَبِعَكَ",
        "answer": "follows you",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "tabiʿaka",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَتْبَعَهُ",
        "answer": "so followed him",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "fa-atbaʿahu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "Follow",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "ittabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "follow",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّبَعْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you follow",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "ittabaʿtum",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّبِعْ",
        "answer": "follow",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "tattabiʿ",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّبِعُونَ",
        "answer": "follow",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "yattabiʿūna",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّبَعُوا",
        "answer": "and follow",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "wa-ittabaʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّبِعُوهُ",
        "answer": "and follow him",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "wa-ittabiʿūhu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّبَعَ",
        "answer": "and followed",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "wa-ittabaʿa",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّبِعُوكُمْ",
        "answer": "will they follow you",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "yattabiʿūkum",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَّبِعُ",
        "answer": "I follow",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "attabiʿu",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهِمُ",
        "answer": "underneath them",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "taḥtihimu",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتْرُكْهُ",
        "answer": "if you leave him",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "tatruk'hu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتْلُ",
        "answer": "And recite",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wa-ut'lu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَمَّتْ",
        "answer": "And was fulfilled",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "watammat",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَمَّ",
        "answer": "so was completed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fatamma",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَتْمَمْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "and We completed them",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wa-atmamnāhā",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُبْتُ",
        "answer": "I turn (in repentance)",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "tub'tu",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَابُوا",
        "answer": "repented",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "tābū",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثُعْبَانٌ",
        "answer": "(was) a serpent",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "thuʿ'bānun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَقُلَتْ",
        "answer": "(will be) heavy",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "thaqulat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَقُلَتْ",
        "answer": "It lays heavily",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "thaqulat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَثْقَلَتْ",
        "answer": "she grows heavy",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "athqalat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثِقَالًا",
        "answer": "heavy",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "thiqālan",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَلَاثِينَ",
        "answer": "thirty",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "thalāthīna",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "الثَّمَرَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) fruits",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-thamarāti",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الثَّمَرَاتِ",
        "answer": "[the] fruits",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-thamarāti",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثْنَتَيْ",
        "answer": "(into) two",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ith'natay",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "اثْنَتَا",
        "answer": "two",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ith'natā",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِبَالَ",
        "answer": "the mountains",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-jibāla",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَبَلِ",
        "answer": "the mountain",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-jabali",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْجَبَلِ",
        "answer": "to the mountain",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "lil'jabali",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَبَلَ",
        "answer": "the mountain",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-jabala",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "اجْتَبَيْتَهَا",
        "answer": "you devised it",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ij'tabaytahā",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاثِمِينَ",
        "answer": "fallen prone",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "jāthimīna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاثِمِينَ",
        "answer": "fallen prone",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "jāthimīna",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْحَدُونَ",
        "answer": "they reject",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yajḥadūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتُجَادِلُونَنِي",
        "answer": "Do you dispute with me",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "atujādilūnanī",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْجَرَادَ",
        "answer": "and the locusts",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-jarāda",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجُرُّهُ",
        "answer": "dragging him",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yajurruhu",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُجْرِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the criminals",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-muj'rimīna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُجْرِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the criminals",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-muj'rimīna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُجْرِمِينَ",
        "answer": "criminal",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "muj'rimīna",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "Flows",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِي",
        "answer": "We recompense",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "najzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِي",
        "answer": "We recompense",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "najzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجْزَوْنَ",
        "answer": "they be recompensed",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yuj'zawna",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجْزِي",
        "answer": "We recompense",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "najzī",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيُجْزَوْنَ",
        "answer": "They will be recompensed",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "sayuj'zawna",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَسَدًا",
        "answer": "an image",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "jasadan",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We made",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "wajaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have made",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "jaʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْعَلْنَا",
        "answer": "place us",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "tajʿalnā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "He made you",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "jaʿalakum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "He made you",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "jaʿalakum",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "اجْعَلْ",
        "answer": "Make",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "ij'ʿal",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَهُ",
        "answer": "He made it",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "jaʿalahu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْعَلْنِي",
        "answer": "place me",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "tajʿalnī",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "and made",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَا",
        "answer": "they make",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "jaʿalā",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجَلَّىٰ",
        "answer": "revealed (His) Glory",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tajallā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُجَلِّيهَا",
        "answer": "can reveal [it]",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yujallīhā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْمَعِينَ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ajmaʿīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْمَعِينَ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ajmaʿīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمْعُكُمْ",
        "answer": "your gathering",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "jamʿukum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَمَلُ",
        "answer": "the camel",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-jamalu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِنِّ",
        "answer": "the jinn",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-jini",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجِنِّ",
        "answer": "the jinn",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-jini",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِنَّةٍ",
        "answer": "(is) any madness",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "jinnatin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةَ",
        "answer": "(in) the Garden",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "l-janata",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Garden",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "Paradise",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةَ",
        "answer": "Paradise",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "l-janata",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةُ",
        "answer": "(is) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "l-janatu",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةَ",
        "answer": "Paradise",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "l-janata",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَهْرِ",
        "answer": "the loudness",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-jahri",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْهَلُونَ",
        "answer": "ignorant",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tajhalūna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَاهِلِينَ",
        "answer": "the ignorant",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "l-jāhilīna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلْيَسْتَجِيبُوا",
        "answer": "and let them respond",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "falyastajībū",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَوَابَ",
        "answer": "(the) answer",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "jawāba",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاوَزْنَا",
        "answer": "And We led across",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wajāwaznā",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَجَاءَهَا",
        "answer": "and came to it",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "fajāahā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "jāahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "comes",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْهُمْ",
        "answer": "comes to them",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "jāathum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْ",
        "answer": "came",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "jāat",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِئْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We had brought them",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "ji'nāhum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْ",
        "answer": "had come",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "jāat",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "has come to you",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "jāakum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "has come to you",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "jāakum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجِئْتَنَا",
        "answer": "Have you come to us",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "aji'tanā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْكُمْ",
        "answer": "has come to you",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "jāatkum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْكُمْ",
        "answer": "has came to you",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "jāatkum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْهُمْ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "jāathum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِئْتُكُمْ",
        "answer": "I (have) come to you",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "ji'tukum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِئْتَ",
        "answer": "come",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "ji'ta",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاءَ",
        "answer": "So came",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "wajāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَاءُوا",
        "answer": "and came (up)",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "wajāū",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْنَا",
        "answer": "they came to us",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "jāatnā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "جِئْتَنَا",
        "answer": "you have come to us",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "ji'tanā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "came to them",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "jāathumu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "came",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "love",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "love",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحِبُّونَ",
        "answer": "you like",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "tuḥibbūna",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَبِطَتْ",
        "answer": "worthless",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ḥabiṭat",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَثِيثًا",
        "answer": "rapidly",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥathīthan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِجَابٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) a partition",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥijābun",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَجَرَ",
        "answer": "the stone",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-ḥajara",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَدِيثٍ",
        "answer": "statement",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ḥadīthin",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَجٌ",
        "answer": "any uneasiness",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ḥarajun",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "has forbidden",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَ",
        "answer": "(had) forbidden",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ḥarrama",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَرَّمَهُمَا",
        "answer": "has forbidden both",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ḥarramahumā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُحَرِّمُ",
        "answer": "and makes unlawful",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wayuḥarrimu",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزَنُونَ",
        "answer": "will grieve",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yaḥzanūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْزَنُونَ",
        "answer": "will grieve",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "taḥzanūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَحْسَبُونَ",
        "answer": "while they think",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "wayaḥsabūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَحْسَنِهَا",
        "answer": "(the) best of it",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "bi-aḥsanihā",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَسَنَاتِ",
        "answer": "with the good",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥasanāti",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُسْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "the best",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "l-ḥus'nā",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحُسْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "the most beautiful",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "l-ḥus'nā",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَسَنَةَ",
        "answer": "the good",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "l-ḥasanata",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَسَنَةُ",
        "answer": "the good",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "l-ḥasanatu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنَةً",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "ḥasanatan",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَاشِرِينَ",
        "answer": "gatherers",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ḥāshirīna",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَاضِرَةَ",
        "answer": "situated",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ḥāḍirata",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِطَّةٌ",
        "answer": "Repentance",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥiṭṭatun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَفِيٌّ",
        "answer": "(were) well informed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥafiyyun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقَّ",
        "answer": "deserved ",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "(will be) the truth",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "[the] right",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "with the truth",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقًّا",
        "answer": "true",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqan",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقًّا",
        "answer": "(to be) true",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqan",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "with the truth",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقَّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقُّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqu",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "[the] right",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "with truth",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقَّ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "with the truth",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقِيقٌ",
        "answer": "Obligated",
        "pcklId": "283",
        "tlit": "ḥaqīqun",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْكُمَ",
        "answer": "judges",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yaḥkuma",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَاكِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] Judges",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "l-ḥākimīna",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُحِلُّ",
        "answer": "and he makes lawful",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wayuḥillu",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُلِيِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their ornaments",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ḥuliyyihim",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمْدُ",
        "answer": "All the praise",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-ḥamdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْمِلْ",
        "answer": "you attack",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "taḥmil",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمَلَتْ",
        "answer": "she carries",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ḥamalat",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَمْلًا",
        "answer": "a burden",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "ḥamlan",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِيتَانُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their fish",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ḥītānuhum",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "wherever",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "where",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "where",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "wherever",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينٍ",
        "answer": "a time",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥīnin",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْيَوْنَ",
        "answer": "you will live",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taḥyawna",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحْيِي",
        "answer": "He gives life",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yuḥ'yī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَسْتَحْيِي",
        "answer": "and we will let live",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "wanastaḥyī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْتَحْيُونَ",
        "answer": "and letting live",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "wayastaḥyūna",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةُ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayatu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَبُثَ",
        "answer": "is bad ",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khabutha",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَبَائِثَ",
        "answer": "the impure things",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-khabāitha",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاخْرُجْ",
        "answer": "So get out",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "fa-ukh'ruj",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "اخْرُجْ",
        "answer": "Get out",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ukh'ruj",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْرُجُ",
        "answer": "comes forth",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yakhruju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْرُجُ",
        "answer": "come forth",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yakhruju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُخْرَجُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be brought forth",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "tukh'rajūna",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْرَجَ",
        "answer": "he drove out",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "akhraja",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْرَجَ",
        "answer": "He has brought forth",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "akhraja",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَخْرَجْنَا",
        "answer": "then We bring forth",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "fa-akhrajnā",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُخْرِجُ",
        "answer": "We will bring forth",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "nukh'riju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْرِجُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "Drive them out",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "akhrijūhum",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنُخْرِجَنَّكَ",
        "answer": "We will surely drive you out",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "lanukh'rijannaka",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْرِجَكُمْ",
        "answer": "drive you out",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "yukh'rijakum",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتُخْرِجُوا",
        "answer": "so that you may drive out",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "litukh'rijū",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخَرَّ",
        "answer": "and fell down",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wakharra",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَاسِئِينَ",
        "answer": "despised",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khāsiīna",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَسِرُوا",
        "answer": "lost",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "khasirū",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَسِرُوا",
        "answer": "they lost",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "khasirū",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the losers",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَخَاسِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(will be) certainly losers",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "lakhāsirūna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the losers",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(who are) the losers",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirūna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the losers",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the losers",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirūna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْصِفَانِ",
        "answer": "(to) fasten",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yakhṣifāni",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَطِيئَاتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your sins",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khaṭīātikum",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَفَّتْ",
        "answer": "(will be) light",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khaffat",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَفِيفًا",
        "answer": "light",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "khafīfan",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخُفْيَةً",
        "answer": "and privately",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wakhuf'yatan",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْلَدَ",
        "answer": "adhered",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "akhlada",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "the immortals",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "will abide forever",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) abide forever",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "khālidūna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِصَةً",
        "answer": "exclusively (for them)",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "khāliṣatan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْلِصِينَ",
        "answer": "(being) sincere",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "mukh'liṣīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "اخْلُفْنِي",
        "answer": "Take my place",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ukh'luf'nī",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَفْتُمُونِي",
        "answer": "you have done in my place",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "khalaftumūnī",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَخَلَفَ",
        "answer": "Then succeeded",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fakhalafa",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَسْتَخْلِفَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and make you successors",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "wayastakhlifakum",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "خِلَافٍ",
        "answer": "opposite (sides)",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "khilāfin",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْفِهِمْ",
        "answer": "behind them",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "khalfihim",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْفٌ",
        "answer": "successors",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "khalfun",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُلَفَاءَ",
        "answer": "successors",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "khulafāa",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُلَفَاءَ",
        "answer": "successors",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "khulafāa",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We created you",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "khalaqnākum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْتَنِي",
        "answer": "You created me",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "khalaqtanī",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخَلَقْتَهُ",
        "answer": "and You created him",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wakhalaqtahu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقْنَا",
        "answer": "We have created",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "khalaqnā",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "has (been) created",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "created you",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "khalaqakum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْلُقُ",
        "answer": "create",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "yakhluqu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْلَقُونَ",
        "answer": "are created",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yukh'laqūna",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَلْقُ",
        "answer": "(is) the creation",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "l-khalqu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَلْقِ",
        "answer": "the stature",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "l-khalqi",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَتْ",
        "answer": "passed away",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "khalat",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "خُوَارٌ",
        "answer": "(had) a lowing sound",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "khuwārun",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَافُ",
        "answer": "[I] fear",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "akhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفٌ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "khawfun",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفٌ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "khawfun",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوْفًا",
        "answer": "(in) fear",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "khawfan",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَخِيفَةً",
        "answer": "and (in) fear",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "wakhīfatan",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاخْتَارَ",
        "answer": "And chose",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-ikh'tāra",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "better",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) best",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Best",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "khayru",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرُ",
        "answer": "(are the) Best",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "khayru",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرُ",
        "answer": "(are) Best",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "khayru",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَيْرِ",
        "answer": "the good",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-khayri",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخِيَاطِ",
        "answer": "(of) the needle",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-khiyāṭi",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَابِرَ",
        "answer": "the roots",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "dābira",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَدْحُورًا",
        "answer": "and expelled",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "madḥūran",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْخُلُوا",
        "answer": "Enter",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ud'khulū",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَخَلَتْ",
        "answer": "entered",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "dakhalat",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْخُلُونَ",
        "answer": "they will enter",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yadkhulūna",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْخُلُوهَا",
        "answer": "they have entered it",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yadkhulūhā",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْخُلُوا",
        "answer": "Enter",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "ud'khulū",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَادْخُلُوا",
        "answer": "and enter",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "wa-ud'khulū",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَدْخِلْنَا",
        "answer": "and admit us",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "wa-adkhil'nā",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنَسْتَدْرِجُهُمْ",
        "answer": "We will gradually lead them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sanastadrijuhum",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَدَرَسُوا",
        "answer": "while they studied",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wadarasū",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادَّارَكُوا",
        "answer": "they had overtaken one another",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "iddārakū",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَادْعُوهُ",
        "answer": "and invoke Him",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wa-id'ʿūhu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "invoke",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "tadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْعُوا",
        "answer": "Call upon",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "id'ʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَادْعُوهُ",
        "answer": "And call Him",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wa-id'ʿūhu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْعُ",
        "answer": "Invoke",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ud'ʿu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَادْعُوهُ",
        "answer": "so invoke Him",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "fa-id'ʿūhu",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَعَوَا",
        "answer": "they both invoke",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "daʿawā",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "you call them",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "tadʿūhum",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدَعَوْتُمُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "whether you call them",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "adaʿawtumūhum",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "you call",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "tadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَادْعُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "So invoke them",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "fa-id'ʿūhum",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْعُوا",
        "answer": "Call",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "id'ʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "you invoke",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "tadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "you call them",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "tadʿūhum",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَعْوَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "their plea",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "daʿwāhum",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَكًّا",
        "answer": "crumbled to dust",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "dakkan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَدَلَّاهُمَا",
        "answer": "So he made both of them fall",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fadallāhumā",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَدَمَّرْنَا",
        "answer": "And We destroyed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wadammarnā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالدَّمَ",
        "answer": "and the blood",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wal-dama",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَدْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "the lower (life)",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-adnā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "[the] world",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their homes",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "dārihim",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَارِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their home(s)",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "dārihim",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَارَ",
        "answer": "(the) home",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "dāra",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالدَّارُ",
        "answer": "And the home",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wal-dāru",
        "frequency": "55",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "beside Him",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "instead of",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) other than",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "dūna",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَدُونَ",
        "answer": "and without",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "wadūna",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينَ",
        "answer": "(in) the religion",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-dīna",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their religion",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "dīnahum",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَذْءُومًا",
        "answer": "disgraced",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "madhūman",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَرَأْنَا",
        "answer": "We have created",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "dharanā",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their descendants",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyatahum",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُرِّيَّةً",
        "answer": "descendants",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "dhurriyyatan",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "And remember",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "So remember",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "fa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "And remember",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "So remember",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "fa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "And remember",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "wa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاذْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "and remember",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "wa-udh'kurū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاذْكُرْ",
        "answer": "And remember",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "wa-udh'kur",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُكِّرُوا",
        "answer": "they had been reminded",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "dhukkirū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "you remember",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "tadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَذَّكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "remember",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "yadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "take heed",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "tadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَذَّكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "receive admonition",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "yadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَذَكَّرُوا",
        "answer": "they remember (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "tadhakkarū",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذِكْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "and a reminder",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "wadhik'rā",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرٌ",
        "answer": "a reminder",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "dhik'run",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرٌ",
        "answer": "a reminder",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "dhik'run",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذِلَّةٌ",
        "answer": "and humiliation",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "wadhillatun",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِذُنُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "for their sins",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "bidhunūbihim",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَاقَا",
        "answer": "they both tasted",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "dhāqā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَذُوقُوا",
        "answer": "so taste",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fadhūqū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَأْسِ",
        "answer": "by head",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "birasi",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "sees you ",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yarākum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَوْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "you see them",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "tarawnahum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَرَاكَ",
        "answer": "surely see you",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "lanarāka",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَرَاكَ",
        "answer": "surely, see you",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "lanarāka",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَانِي",
        "answer": "you (can) see Me",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "tarānī",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَانِي",
        "answer": "you (will) see Me",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "tarānī",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَوْا",
        "answer": "they see",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yaraw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَأَوْا",
        "answer": "and they saw",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "wara-aw",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "And you see them",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "watarāhum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُرِيَهُمَا",
        "answer": "to show both of them",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "liyuriyahumā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرِنِي",
        "answer": "Show me",
        "pcklId": "281",
        "tlit": "arinī",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَأُرِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "I will show you",
        "pcklId": "282",
        "tlit": "sa-urīkum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمَا",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "rabbukumā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّهُمَا",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "rabbuhumā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "(by) my Lord",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّيَ",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "rabbiya",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "(of) our Lord",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "rabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّنَا",
        "answer": "our Lord",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "rabbunā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "(by) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "(of) our Lord",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "rabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكُمُ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "rabbakumu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّ",
        "answer": "Lord",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "rabbu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "rabbakum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) its Lord",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "(of) my Lord",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "(of) my Lord",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their Lord",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "(of) my Lord",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّنَا",
        "answer": "our Lord",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "rabbunā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّنَا",
        "answer": "(by) Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "rabbunā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "(of) my Lord",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّ",
        "answer": "in (the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "birabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "Lord",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "122"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "our Lord",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "rabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّنَا",
        "answer": "(of) our Lord",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "rabbinā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "rabbanā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord ",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) his Lord",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "rabbuhu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "O my Lord",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "rabbuhu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّنَا",
        "answer": "Our Lord",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "rabbunā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "O my Lord",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "of their Lord",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "lirabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "O my Lord",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "222",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكَ",
        "answer": "(by) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "rabbuka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "birabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُمَا",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "rabbahumā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "rabbika",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْبَعِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) forty",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "arbaʿīna",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّجْزُ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-rij'zu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّجْزَ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-rij'za",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّجْزَ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-rij'za",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجْزًا",
        "answer": "torment",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "rij'zan",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجْسٌ",
        "answer": "punishment",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "rij'sun",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجَعَ",
        "answer": "returned",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "rajaʿa",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجِعُونَ",
        "answer": "return",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yarjiʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْجِعُونَ",
        "answer": "return",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yarjiʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّجْفَةُ",
        "answer": "the earthquake",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-rajfatu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّجْفَةُ",
        "answer": "the earthquake",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-rajfatu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّجْفَةُ",
        "answer": "the earthquake",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "l-rajfatu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجَالٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) men",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "rijālun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِجَالًا",
        "answer": "(to) men",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "rijālan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّجَالَ",
        "answer": "the men",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-rijāla",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجُلٍ",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "rajulin",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجُلٍ",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "rajulin",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجُلًا",
        "answer": "men",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "rajulan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرْجُلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your feet",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "wa-arjulakum",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْجُلٌ",
        "answer": "feet",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "arjulun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْجِهْ",
        "answer": "Postpone him",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "arjih",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرْحَمْنَا",
        "answer": "and have mercy (on) us",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "watarḥamnā",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْحَمُونَ",
        "answer": "receive mercy",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "tur'ḥamūna",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْحَمْنَا",
        "answer": "has Mercy on us",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yarḥamnā",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَارْحَمْنَا",
        "answer": "and have mercy upon us",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wa-ir'ḥamnā",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْحَمُونَ",
        "answer": "receive mercy",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tur'ḥamūna",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْحَمُ",
        "answer": "(are) the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "arḥamu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَحْمَةٍ",
        "answer": "Mercy",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "biraḥmatin",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَةً",
        "answer": "and mercy",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatan",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتَ",
        "answer": "(the) Mercy",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "raḥmata",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتِهِ",
        "answer": "His Mercy",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "raḥmatihi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَحْمَةٍ",
        "answer": "by Mercy",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "biraḥmatin",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتِكَ",
        "answer": "Your Mercy",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "raḥmatika",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَةٌ",
        "answer": "and mercy",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَتِي",
        "answer": "but My Mercy",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatī",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَحْمَةٌ",
        "answer": "and mercy",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "waraḥmatun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "251",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحِيمٌ",
        "answer": "Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "252",
        "tlit": "raḥīmun",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّاحِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the merciful",
        "pcklId": "333",
        "tlit": "l-rāḥimīna",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُرَدُّ",
        "answer": "we are sent back",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "nuraddu",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقَكُمُ",
        "answer": "(has been) provided (to) you",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "razaqakumu",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَزَقْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We have provided you",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "razaqnākum",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّزْقِ",
        "answer": "sustenance",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "l-riz'qi",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُرْسِلَ",
        "answer": "were sent",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ur'sila",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرْسِلُ",
        "answer": "sends",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yur'silu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُرْسِلَ",
        "answer": "he has been sent",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ur'sila",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُرْسِلْتُ",
        "answer": "I have been sent",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ur'sil'tu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We sent",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَرْسِلْ",
        "answer": "so send",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "fa-arsil",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرْسِلْ",
        "answer": "and send",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wa-arsil",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "So We sent",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "fa-arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَنُرْسِلَنَّ",
        "answer": "and surely, we will send",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "walanur'silanna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَرْسَلْنَا",
        "answer": "So We sent",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "fa-arsalnā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِسَالَاتِ",
        "answer": "the Messages",
        "pcklId": "130",
        "tlit": "risālāti",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِسَالَاتِ",
        "answer": "Messages",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "risālāti",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِسَالَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) Messages",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "risālāti",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "رِسَالَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) Message",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "risālata",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرِسَالَاتِي",
        "answer": "with My Messages",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "birisālātī",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلٌ",
        "answer": "Messengers",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "rusulun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلُنَا",
        "answer": "Our messengers (Angels)",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "rusulunā",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلُ",
        "answer": "Messengers",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "rusulu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلُ",
        "answer": "(the) Messengers",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "rusulu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٌ",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "rasūlun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٌ",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "rasūlun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their Messengers",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "rusuluhum",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولٌ",
        "answer": "a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "rasūlun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّسُولَ",
        "answer": "the Messenger",
        "pcklId": "235",
        "tlit": "l-rasūla",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولُ",
        "answer": "(the) Messenger",
        "pcklId": "236",
        "tlit": "rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "237",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "480",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُرْسَلٌ",
        "answer": "(is the) one sent",
        "pcklId": "481",
        "tlit": "mur'salun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُرْسَلِينَ",
        "answer": "the Messengers",
        "pcklId": "482",
        "tlit": "l-mur'salīna",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُرْسَاهَا",
        "answer": "its appointed time",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "mur'sāhā",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرُّشْدِ",
        "answer": "(of) the righteousness",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-rush'di",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَرَفَعْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "surely, We (could) have raised him",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "larafaʿnāhu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْهَبُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) fearful",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yarhabūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَرْهَبُوهُمْ",
        "answer": "and terrified them",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-is'tarhabūhum",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّيَاحَ",
        "answer": "the winds",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-riyāḥa",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُ",
        "answer": "He wants",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "yurīdu",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "110"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرِيشًا",
        "answer": "and (as) an adornment",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "warīshan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الزَّكَاةَ",
        "answer": "zakah",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-zakata",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَوْجُكَ",
        "answer": "and your wife",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wazawjuka",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَوْجَهَا",
        "answer": "its mate",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "zawjahā",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَزَادَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and increased you",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wazādakum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنَزِيدُ",
        "answer": "We will increase (reward)",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "sanazīdu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "زِينَتَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your adornment",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "zīnatakum",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "زِينَةَ",
        "answer": "(the) adornment",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "zīnata",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَنَسْأَلَنَّ",
        "answer": "Then surely We will question",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "falanasalanna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَنَسْأَلَنَّ",
        "answer": "and surely We will question",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "walanasalanna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْأَلْهُمْ",
        "answer": "And ask them",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wasalhum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "They ask you",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْأَلُونَكَ",
        "answer": "They ask you",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yasalūnaka",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْبِتُونَ",
        "answer": "they had Sabbath",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yasbitūna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّبْتِ",
        "answer": "the (matter of) Sabbath",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-sabti",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their Sabbath",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "sabtihim",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُسَبِّحُونَهُ",
        "answer": "And they glorify Him",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wayusabbiḥūnahu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَكَ",
        "answer": "Glory be to You",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥānaka",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْبَاطًا",
        "answer": "tribes",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "asbāṭan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبْعِينَ",
        "answer": "seventy",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "sabʿīna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبَقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "has preceded you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sabaqakum",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلَ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "sabīla",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلَ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "sabīla",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "(as) a way",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلَ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "sabīla",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "(as) a way",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلًا",
        "answer": "(to) a way",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "sabīlan",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِتَّةِ",
        "answer": "six",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "sittati",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْجُدُوا",
        "answer": "Prostrate",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "us'judū",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَجَدُوا",
        "answer": "So they prostrated",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fasajadū",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْجُدَ",
        "answer": "you prostrate",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "tasjuda",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْجُدُونَ",
        "answer": "they prostrate",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yasjudūna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْجِدٍ",
        "answer": "masjid",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "masjidin",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسْجِدٍ",
        "answer": "masjid",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "masjidin",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاجِدِينَ",
        "answer": "those who prostrated",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-sājidīna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاجِدِينَ",
        "answer": "prostrate",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "sājidīna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُجَّدًا",
        "answer": "prostrating",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "sujjadan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَحَابًا",
        "answer": "clouds ",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "saḥāban",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَحَرُوا",
        "answer": "they bewitched",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "saḥarū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتَسْحَرَنَا",
        "answer": "so that you bewitch us",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "litasḥaranā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسِحْرٍ",
        "answer": "with a magic",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bisiḥ'rin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَسَاحِرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely a magician ",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "lasāḥirun",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاحِرٍ",
        "answer": "magician",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "sāḥirin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّحَرَةُ",
        "answer": "the magicians",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-saḥaratu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّحَرَةُ",
        "answer": "the magicians",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-saḥaratu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسَخَّرَاتٍ",
        "answer": "subjected",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "musakharātin",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّرَّاءُ",
        "answer": "and the ease",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "wal-sarāu",
        "frequency": "44",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَسَرِيعُ",
        "answer": "(is) surely swift",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "lasarīʿu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُسْرِفُوا",
        "answer": "be extravagant",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tus'rifū",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْرِفِينَ",
        "answer": "the extravagant ones",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-mus'rifīna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْرِفُونَ",
        "answer": "(who) commit excesses",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "mus'rifūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَفَاهَةٍ",
        "answer": "foolishness",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "safāhatin",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَفَاهَةٌ",
        "answer": "foolishness",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "safāhatun",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّفَهَاءُ",
        "answer": "the foolish",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-sufahāu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُقِطَ",
        "answer": "(it was made to) fall",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "suqiṭa",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَسْقَاهُ",
        "answer": "asked him for water",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "is'tasqāhu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَكَتَ",
        "answer": "was calmed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sakata",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْكُنْ",
        "answer": "Dwell",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "us'kun",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْكُنُوا",
        "answer": "Live",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "us'kunū",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيَسْكُنَ",
        "answer": "that he might live",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "liyaskuna",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْسَلَخَ",
        "answer": "but he detached",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fa-insalakha",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُلْطَانًا",
        "answer": "any authority",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "sul'ṭānan",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُلْطَانٍ",
        "answer": "authority",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "sul'ṭānin",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَامٌ",
        "answer": "Peace",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "salāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْلِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(as) Muslims",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "mus'limīna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّلْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "and the quails",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-salwā",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "hear",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "they hear",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) hear",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْمَعُوا",
        "answer": "do they not",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "yasmaʿū",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَمِعُوا",
        "answer": "then listen",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "fa-is'tamiʿū",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِيعٌ",
        "answer": "(is) All-Hearing",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "samīʿun",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمِّ",
        "answer": "(the) eye",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "sammi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَمَّيْتُمُوهَا",
        "answer": "you have named them ",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "sammaytumūhā",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْمَاءٍ",
        "answer": "names",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "asmāin",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَسْمَاءُ",
        "answer": "(are) the names ",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-asmāu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْمَائِهِ",
        "answer": "His names",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "asmāihi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heaven",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the heaven",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "104",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "105",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالسِّنِينَ",
        "answer": "with years (of famine)",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "bil-sinīna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُهُولِهَا",
        "answer": "its plains",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "suhūlihā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاءَ",
        "answer": "Evil",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "sāa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسُوءٍ",
        "answer": "with harm",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "bisūin",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُوءَ",
        "answer": "(with) worst",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "sūa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّوءِ",
        "answer": "the evil",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "l-sūi",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُوءَ",
        "answer": "(with) a grievous",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "sūa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّوءُ",
        "answer": "the evil",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-sūu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوْآتِهِمَا",
        "answer": "their shame",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "sawātihimā",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوْآتُهُمَا",
        "answer": "their shame",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "sawātuhumā",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوْآتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your shame",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "sawātikum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوْآتِهِمَا",
        "answer": "their shame",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "sawātihimā",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّيِّئَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the bad",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "l-sayi-ati",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَةٌ",
        "answer": "bad",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "sayyi-atun",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّيِّئَاتِ",
        "answer": "the evil deeds",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "l-sayiāti",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّيِّئَاتِ",
        "answer": "and the bad",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "wal-sayiāti",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاعَةِ",
        "answer": "the Hour",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-sāʿati",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاعَةً",
        "answer": "an hour",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "sāʿatan",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُقْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We drive them",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "suq'nāhu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسُومُونَكُمْ",
        "answer": "who were afflicting you",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yasūmūnakum",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسُومُهُمْ",
        "answer": "would afflict them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yasūmuhum",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسِيمَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "by their marks",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "bisīmāhum",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسِيمَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "by their marks",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "bisīmāhum",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَوَىٰ",
        "answer": "He ascended",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "is'tawā",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَوَاءٌ",
        "answer": "(It is) same",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "sawāon",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّجَرَةَ",
        "answer": "[the] tree",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-shajarata",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّجَرَةِ",
        "answer": "[the] tree",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-shajarati",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّجَرَةَ",
        "answer": "the tree",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-shajarata",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّجَرَةِ",
        "answer": "[the] tree",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-shajarati",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَدِيدًا",
        "answer": "severe",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "shadīdan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاشْرَبُوا",
        "answer": "and drink",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wa-ish'rabū",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَشْرَبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their drinking place",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "mashrabahum",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَّعًا",
        "answer": "visibly",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "shurraʿan",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَشَارِقَ",
        "answer": "(the) eastern (parts)",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "mashāriqa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُشْرِكُوا",
        "answer": "you associate (others)",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "tush'rikū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْرَكَ",
        "answer": "partners (were) associated (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ashraka",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "they associate (with Him)",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "Do they associate",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ayush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَاءَ",
        "answer": "partners",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "shurakāa",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your partners",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "shurakāakum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانَ",
        "answer": "[the] Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "[the] Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيَاطِينَ",
        "answer": "the devils",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-shayāṭīna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيَاطِينَ",
        "answer": "the devils",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-shayāṭīna",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانُ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانِ",
        "answer": "[the] Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّيْطَانِ",
        "answer": "the Shaitaan",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-shayṭāni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْعُرُونَ",
        "answer": "perceive",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yashʿurūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَشْفَعُوا",
        "answer": "so (that) they intercede",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "fayashfaʿū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُفَعَاءَ",
        "answer": "intercessors",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "shufaʿāa",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "you (are) grateful",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "tashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْكُرُونَ",
        "answer": "who are grateful",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "yashkurūna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاكِرِينَ",
        "answer": "grateful",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "shākirīna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّاكِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the grateful",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "l-shākirīna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّاكِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the thankful",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "l-shākirīna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُشْمِتْ",
        "answer": "rejoice",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "tush'mit",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّمْسَ",
        "answer": "and the sun",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wal-shamsa",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَمَائِلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their left",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "shamāilihim",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَشَهِدُوا",
        "answer": "and they (will) testify",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "washahidū",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهِدْنَا",
        "answer": "we have testified",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "shahid'nā",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَشْهَدَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and made them testify",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "wa-ashhadahum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَهْوَةً",
        "answer": "lustfully",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "shahwatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِئْتُمَا",
        "answer": "you both wish",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "shi'tumā",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءَ",
        "answer": "wills",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "yashāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "We willed",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "nashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِئْتَ",
        "answer": "you (had) willed",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "shi'ta",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "You will",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "tashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "You will",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "tashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "I will",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "ashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِئْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you wish",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "shi'tum",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِئْنَا",
        "answer": "We willed",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "shi'nā",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "wills",
        "pcklId": "76",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْيَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "in their things",
        "pcklId": "322",
        "tlit": "ashyāahum",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "323",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "324",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "325",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "thing",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "(every)thing",
        "pcklId": "327",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "328",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "191"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصْبَحُوا",
        "answer": "then they became",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣbaḥū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "78"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصْبَحُوا",
        "answer": "then they became",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣbaḥū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "91"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاصْبِرُوا",
        "answer": "then be patient",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fa-iṣ'birū",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاصْبِرُوا",
        "answer": "and be patient",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wa-iṣ'birū",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبَرُوا",
        "answer": "they were patient",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ṣabarū",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَبْرًا",
        "answer": "patience",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "ṣabran",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(are the) companions",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(the) companions",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابَ",
        "answer": "(to the) companions",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "aṣḥāba",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابَ",
        "answer": "(to the) companions",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "aṣḥāba",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) companions",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(the) companions",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابُ",
        "answer": "(the) companions",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābu",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابَ",
        "answer": "(to the) companions",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "aṣḥāba",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِصَاحِبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "in their companion",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "biṣāḥibihim",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصُدُّونَ",
        "answer": "hinder",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yaṣuddūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَصُدُّونَ",
        "answer": "and hindering",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wataṣuddūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدْرِكَ",
        "answer": "your breast",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ṣadrika",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُدُورِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their breasts",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ṣudūrihim",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the truthful",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "l-ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the truthful",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "l-ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَادِقِينَ",
        "answer": "truthful",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "ṣādiqīna",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطَكَ",
        "answer": "(on) Your path",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭaka",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطٍ",
        "answer": "path",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭin",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "صُرِفَتْ",
        "answer": "are turned",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṣurifat",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَأَصْرِفُ",
        "answer": "I will turn away",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "sa-aṣrifu",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُصَرِّفُ",
        "answer": "We explain",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "nuṣarrifu",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَعِقًا",
        "answer": "unconscious",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "ṣaʿiqan",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّاغِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disgraced ones",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāghirīna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَاغِرِينَ",
        "answer": "humiliated",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "ṣāghirīna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "اصْطَفَيْتُكَ",
        "answer": "have chosen you",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "iṣ'ṭafaytuka",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأُصَلِّبَنَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "I will surely crucify you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "la-uṣallibannakum",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْلَحَ",
        "answer": "and reforms",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣlaḥa",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَصْلِحْ",
        "answer": "and do right",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wa-aṣliḥ",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "Salih",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "Salih",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا صَالِحُ",
        "answer": "O Salih",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yāṣāliḥu",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the righteous",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥūna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "a righteous (child)",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَالِحًا",
        "answer": "a good, (child)",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "ṣāliḥan",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّالِحَاتِ",
        "answer": "[the] righteous deeds",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "l-ṣāliḥāti",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِصْلَاحِهَا",
        "answer": "its reformation",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "iṣ'lāḥihā",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِصْلَاحِهَا",
        "answer": "its reformation",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "iṣ'lāḥihā",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُصْلِحِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the reformers",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "l-muṣ'liḥīna",
        "frequency": "180",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّلَاةَ",
        "answer": "the prayer",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "l-ṣalata",
        "frequency": "99",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَامِتُونَ",
        "answer": "remain silent",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ṣāmitūna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصْنَعُ",
        "answer": "make",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaṣnaʿu",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْنَامٍ",
        "answer": "idols",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "aṣnāmin",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصَبْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We (could) afflict them",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "aṣabnāhum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُصِبْهُمْ",
        "answer": "afflicts them",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "tuṣib'hum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُصِيبُ",
        "answer": "I afflict",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "uṣību",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَوَّرْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We fashioned you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṣawwarnākum",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضُحًى",
        "answer": "(in) daylight",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ḍuḥan",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "اضْرِبْ",
        "answer": "Strike",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "iḍ'rib",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرًّا",
        "answer": "(power to) harm",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "ḍarran",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالضَّرَّاءِ",
        "answer": "and hardship",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "wal-ḍarāi",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضَّرَّاءُ",
        "answer": "the adversity",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "l-ḍarāu",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضَّرَّعُونَ",
        "answer": "(become) humble",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaḍḍarraʿūna",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَضَرُّعًا",
        "answer": "humbly",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "taḍarruʿan",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَضَرُّعًا",
        "answer": "humbly",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "taḍarruʿan",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتُضْعِفُوا",
        "answer": "were oppressed ",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "us'tuḍ'ʿifū",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسْتَضْعَفُونَ",
        "answer": "considered weak ",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yus'taḍʿafūna",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَضْعَفُونِي",
        "answer": "considered me weak",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "is'taḍʿafūnī",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضِعْفٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a double",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ḍiʿ'fun",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضِعْفًا",
        "answer": "double",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ḍiʿ'fan",
        "frequency": "52",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالضَّفَادِعَ",
        "answer": "and the frogs",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-ḍafādiʿa",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلُّوا",
        "answer": "They strayed",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ḍallū",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَضَلَّ",
        "answer": "and strayed",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "waḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلُّوا",
        "answer": "gone astray",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ḍallū",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضَلُّونَا",
        "answer": "misled us",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "aḍallūnā",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُضِلُّ",
        "answer": "You let go astray",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "tuḍillu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضْلِلْ",
        "answer": "He lets go astray",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "yuḍ'lil",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضْلِلِ",
        "answer": "(is) let go astray",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "yuḍ'lili",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَضَلُّ",
        "answer": "(are) more astray",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "aḍallu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَالٍ",
        "answer": "error",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "ḍalālin",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضَّلَالَةُ",
        "answer": "the astraying",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "l-ḍalālatu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَالَةٌ",
        "answer": "error",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "ḍalālatun",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُضِيعُ",
        "answer": "[We] let go waste",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nuḍīʿu",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَطْبَعُ",
        "answer": "and We put a seal",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wanaṭbaʿu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطْبَعُ",
        "answer": "(has been) put a seal",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaṭbaʿu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "طُغْيَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their transgression",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ṭugh'yānihim",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطَفِقَا",
        "answer": "and they began",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waṭafiqā",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطْلُبُهُ",
        "answer": "seeking it",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaṭlubuhu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطْمَعُونَ",
        "answer": "hope",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaṭmaʿūna",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطَمَعًا",
        "answer": "and hope",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "waṭamaʿan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَطَهَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "who keep themselves pure",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yataṭahharūna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَطِيعُونَ",
        "answer": "they are able",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "yastaṭīʿūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "192"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَطِيعُونَ",
        "answer": "they are able",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "yastaṭīʿūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِفَةٌ",
        "answer": "a group",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ṭāifatun",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَطَائِفَةٌ",
        "answer": "and a group",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "waṭāifatun",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطُّوفَانَ",
        "answer": "the flood",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-ṭūfāna",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِفٌ",
        "answer": "an evil thought",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "ṭāifun",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّيِّبُ",
        "answer": "[the] pure",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-ṭayibu",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالطَّيِّبَاتِ",
        "answer": "and the pure things",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wal-ṭayibāti",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّيِّبَاتِ",
        "answer": "the pure things",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-ṭayibāti",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيِّبَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) good things",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ṭayyibāti",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَطَّيَّرُوا",
        "answer": "they ascribe evil omens",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaṭṭayyarū",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their evil omens",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "ṭāiruhum",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "طِينٍ",
        "answer": "clay",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "ṭīnin",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظَلَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "And We shaded",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "waẓallalnā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلَّةٌ",
        "answer": "a canopy",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ẓullatun",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(doing) injustice",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yaẓlimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمْنَا",
        "answer": "we have wronged",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "ẓalamnā",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "But they were unjust",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "faẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُونَا",
        "answer": "they wronged Us",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ẓalamūnā",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "doing wrong",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yaẓlimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "wronged",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "doing wrong",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yaẓlimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "wronged",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "ẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَظْلِمُونَ",
        "answer": "wrong",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "yaẓlimūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) more unjust",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "aẓlamu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "291",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(who are) wrongdoing",
        "pcklId": "292",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَظُنُّكَ",
        "answer": "[we] think you",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "lanaẓunnuka",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَظَنُّوا",
        "answer": "and they thought",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "waẓannū",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَهَرَ",
        "answer": "(is) apparent",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ẓahara",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُهُورِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their loins ",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ẓuhūrihim",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "Worship",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "uʿ'budū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "Worship",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "uʿ'budū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَعْبُدَ",
        "answer": "that we (should) worship",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "linaʿbuda",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْبُدُ",
        "answer": "worship",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "yaʿbudu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "Worship",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "uʿ'budū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "Worship",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "uʿ'budū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادَتِهِ",
        "answer": "His worship",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "ʿibādatihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِعِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "for His slaves",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "liʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "His servants",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "ʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادٌ",
        "answer": "(are) slaves",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "ʿibādun",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَتَوْا",
        "answer": "and (were) insolent",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waʿataw",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَتَوْا",
        "answer": "they exceeded all bounds",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ʿataw",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْثَوْا",
        "answer": "act wickedly",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "taʿthaw",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَعَجِبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Do you wonder",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "awaʿajib'tum",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَعَجِبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Do you wonder",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "awaʿajib'tum",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعَجِلْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Were you impatient",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aʿajil'tum",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِجْلًا",
        "answer": "a calf ",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ʿij'lan",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِجْلَ",
        "answer": "the calf",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-ʿij'la",
        "frequency": "47",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْدِلُونَ",
        "answer": "establishes justice",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yaʿdilūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْدِلُونَ",
        "answer": "they establish justice",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yaʿdilūna",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْدُونَ",
        "answer": "they transgressed",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaʿdūna",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) an enemy",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوٌّ",
        "answer": "(as) enemy",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwun",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your enemy",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwakum",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْدَاءَ",
        "answer": "the enemies",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-aʿdāa",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُعْتَدِينَ",
        "answer": "the transgressors",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "l-muʿ'tadīna",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "punishment",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابَ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابَ",
        "answer": "punishment",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) torment",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابِي",
        "answer": "My punishment ",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābī",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابًا",
        "answer": "(with) a punishment",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāban",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "with a punishment",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "biʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "[the] punishment",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُعَذِّبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "punish them",
        "pcklId": "365",
        "tlit": "muʿadhibuhum",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعْذِرَةً",
        "answer": "To be absolved",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "maʿdhiratan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْرِشُونَ",
        "answer": "erect",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaʿrishūna",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَرْشِ",
        "answer": "the Throne",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-ʿarshi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعْرِضْ",
        "answer": "and turn away",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿriḍ",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرَضَ",
        "answer": "goods",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "ʿaraḍa",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرَضٌ",
        "answer": "goods",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "ʿaraḍun",
        "frequency": "79",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْرِفُونَ",
        "answer": "recognizing",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "yaʿrifūna",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْرِفُونَهُمْ",
        "answer": "whom they recognize",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "yaʿrifūnahum",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْرَافِ",
        "answer": "the heights",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "l-aʿrāfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَعْرَافِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heights",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-aʿrāfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْعُرْفِ",
        "answer": "the good",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "bil-ʿur'fi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْمَعْرُوفِ",
        "answer": "to the right",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "bil-maʿrūfi",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَزَّرُوهُ",
        "answer": "and honor him",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waʿazzarūhu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَسَىٰ",
        "answer": "Perhaps",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "ʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَسَىٰ",
        "answer": "perhaps",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ʿasā",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَشْرٍ",
        "answer": "with ten (more)",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "biʿashrin",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَشْرَةَ",
        "answer": "(and) ten [i.e. twelve]",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ʿashrata",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَشْرَةَ",
        "answer": "(and) ten [i.e. twelve]",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ʿashrata",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَصَاهُ",
        "answer": "his staff",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ʿaṣāhu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَصَاكَ",
        "answer": "your staff",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿaṣāka",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَصَاكَ",
        "answer": "with your staff",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "biʿaṣāka",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٍ",
        "answer": "Great",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmin",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٍ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmin",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٌ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmun",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَفَوْا",
        "answer": "they increased",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ʿafaw",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَفْوَ",
        "answer": "(to) forgiveness",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "l-ʿafwa",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "199"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاقِبَةُ",
        "answer": "(the) end",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ʿāqibatu",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاقِبَةُ",
        "answer": "(the) end",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ʿāqibatu",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَاقِبَةُ",
        "answer": "(the) end",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ʿāqibatu",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْعَاقِبَةُ",
        "answer": "And the end",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wal-ʿāqibatu",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعِقَابِ",
        "answer": "(in) the retribution",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "l-ʿiqābi",
        "frequency": "80",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَقَرُوا",
        "answer": "Then they hamstrung",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faʿaqarū",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "you use intellect",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "taʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْكُفُونَ",
        "answer": "devoted",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yaʿkufūna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "who know",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "and I know",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "wa-aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "Do you know",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "ataʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you will know",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِمَ",
        "answer": "knew",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "ʿalima",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "they know",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "494",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "495",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "496",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "the worlds",
        "pcklId": "497",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "498",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "499",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "the worlds",
        "pcklId": "500",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعِلْمٍ",
        "answer": "with knowledge",
        "pcklId": "577",
        "tlit": "biʿil'min",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمٍ",
        "answer": "knowledge ",
        "pcklId": "578",
        "tlit": "ʿil'min",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمًا",
        "answer": "(in) knowledge",
        "pcklId": "579",
        "tlit": "ʿil'man",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمُهَا",
        "answer": "its knowledge",
        "pcklId": "580",
        "tlit": "ʿil'muhā",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمُهَا",
        "answer": "its knowledge",
        "pcklId": "581",
        "tlit": "ʿil'muhā",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "learned",
        "pcklId": "685",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٍ",
        "answer": "learned",
        "pcklId": "686",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmin",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "All-Knowing",
        "pcklId": "687",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَعَالَى",
        "answer": "But exalted",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "fataʿālā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "190"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "and do",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "waʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنَعْمَلَ",
        "answer": "so (that) we do (deeds)",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "fanaʿmala",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعْمَلُ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "naʿmalu",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you will do",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "ʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(are) their deeds",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "aʿmāluhum",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَهُونَ",
        "answer": "wandering blindly",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yaʿmahūna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِينَ",
        "answer": "blind",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ʿamīna",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "at",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "at",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(are) with",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "ʿindaka",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَهُمْ",
        "answer": "with them",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "ʿindahum",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(is) with",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(is) with",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "(are) near",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَهِدَ",
        "answer": "He has promised",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿahida",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَهْدٍ",
        "answer": "covenant",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ʿahdin",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِوَجًا",
        "answer": "crookedness",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ʿiwajan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِوَجًا",
        "answer": "crooked",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ʿiwajan",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعُودُونَ",
        "answer": "(so) will you return",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "taʿūdūna",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَتَعُودُنَّ",
        "answer": "you must return",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "lataʿūdunna",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "عُدْنَا",
        "answer": "we returned",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ʿud'nā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعُودَ",
        "answer": "we return",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "naʿūda",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَادٍ",
        "answer": "Aad",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "ʿādin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَادٍ",
        "answer": "Aad",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "ʿādin",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَعِذْ",
        "answer": "then seek refuge",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "fa-is'taʿidh",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَعِينُوا",
        "answer": "Seek help",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "is'taʿīnū",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَعَايِشَ",
        "answer": "livelihood",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "maʿāyisha",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْيُنَ",
        "answer": "(the) eyes",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "aʿyuna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَيْنًا",
        "answer": "springs",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ʿaynan",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْيُنٌ",
        "answer": "(are) eyes",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "aʿyunun",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْيُنٌ",
        "answer": "eyes",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "aʿyunun",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَابِرِينَ",
        "answer": "those who stayed behind",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-ghābirīna",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْغُدُوِّ",
        "answer": "in the mornings",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "bil-ghuduwi",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَغَارِبَهَا",
        "answer": "and the western (parts) of it",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wamaghāribahā",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَغَرَّتْهُمُ",
        "answer": "and deluded them",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wagharrathumu",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغُرُورٍ",
        "answer": "by deception",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "bighurūrin",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَغْرَقْنَا",
        "answer": "And We drowned",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wa-aghraqnā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَغْرَقْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and We drowned them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fa-aghraqnāhum",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُغْشِي",
        "answer": "He covers",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yugh'shī",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَغَشَّاهَا",
        "answer": "he covers her",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "taghashāhā",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَوَاشٍ",
        "answer": "coverings",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "ghawāshin",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَغَضَبٌ",
        "answer": "and anger",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "waghaḍabun",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَضَبٌ",
        "answer": "wrath",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ghaḍabun",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَضَبُ",
        "answer": "the anger",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-ghaḍabu",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَضْبَانَ",
        "answer": "angry",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "ghaḍbāna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "You forgive",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "taghfir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "and forgive",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wayaghfir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "اغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "Forgive",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "igh'fir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "so forgive",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "fa-igh'fir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "We will forgive",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "naghfir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيُغْفَرُ",
        "answer": "It will be forgiven",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "sayugh'faru",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَغَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "laghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "153"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَغَفُورٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "laghafūrun",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) Forgivers",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "l-ghāfirīna",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَافِلِينَ",
        "answer": "heedless",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ghāfilīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَافِلِينَ",
        "answer": "heedless",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "ghāfilīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَافِلِينَ",
        "answer": "unaware",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "ghāfilīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَافِلُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the heedless",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-ghāfilūna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَافِلِينَ",
        "answer": "the heedless",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-ghāfilīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَغُلِبُوا",
        "answer": "So they were defeated",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "faghulibū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَالِبِينَ",
        "answer": "the victors",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "l-ghālibīna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "غِلٍّ",
        "answer": "malice",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ghillin",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَغْلَالَ",
        "answer": "and the fetters",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wal-aghlāla",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَمَامَ",
        "answer": "(with) the clouds",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-ghamāma",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "(has) availed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "aghnā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَغْنَوْا",
        "answer": "they (had) lived",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yaghnaw",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْوَيْتَنِي",
        "answer": "You have sent me astray",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "aghwaytanī",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيِّ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] error",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-ghayi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيِّ",
        "answer": "the error",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-ghayi",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "202"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَاوِينَ",
        "answer": "those gone astray",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "l-ghāwīna",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيْبَ",
        "answer": "(of) the unseen",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-ghayba",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَائِبِينَ",
        "answer": "absent",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "ghāibīna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "other than",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُهُ",
        "answer": "other than Him",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ghayruhu",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُهُ",
        "answer": "other than Him",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ghayruhu",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُهُ",
        "answer": "other than Him",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "ghayruhu",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرُهُ",
        "answer": "other than Him",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "ghayruhu",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغَيْرَ",
        "answer": "Should other than",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "aghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "other than",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَحْ",
        "answer": "Decide",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "if'taḥ",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَفَتَحْنَا",
        "answer": "surely We (would have) opened",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "lafataḥnā",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُفَتَّحُ",
        "answer": "be opened",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "tufattaḥu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاتِحِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who Decide",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-fātiḥīna",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْتِنَنَّكُمُ",
        "answer": "tempt you",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yaftinannakumu",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَتُكَ",
        "answer": "Your trial",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "fit'natuka",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاحِشَةً",
        "answer": "immorality",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fāḥishatan",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَوَاحِشَ",
        "answer": "the shameful deeds",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-fawāḥisha",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاحِشَةَ",
        "answer": "(such) immorality",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-fāḥishata",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْفَحْشَاءِ",
        "answer": "immorality",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "bil-faḥshāi",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفْرِغْ",
        "answer": "Pour",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "afrigh",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرِيقًا",
        "answer": "A group",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "farīqan",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَرِيقًا",
        "answer": "and a group",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "wafarīqan",
        "frequency": "72",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "invented",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "if'tarā",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْتَرُونَ",
        "answer": "invent",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yaftarūna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَرَيْنَا",
        "answer": "we would have fabricated",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "if'taraynā",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْتَرِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones who invent (falsehood)",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-muf'tarīna",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُفْسِدُوا",
        "answer": "cause corruption",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "tuf'sidū",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُفْسِدُوا",
        "answer": "cause corruption",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tuf'sidū",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُفْسِدُوا",
        "answer": "so that they cause corruption",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "liyuf'sidū",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُفْسِدِينَ",
        "answer": "spreading corruption",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "muf'sidīna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْسِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the corrupters",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "l-muf'sidīna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْسِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the corrupters",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "l-muf'sidīna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْسِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the corrupters",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-muf'sidīna",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْسُقُونَ",
        "answer": "defiantly disobeying",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yafsuqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْسُقُونَ",
        "answer": "defiantly disobeying",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yafsuqūna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَفَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "certainly, defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "lafāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُفَصِّلُ",
        "answer": "We explain",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "nufaṣṣilu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصَّلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "which We have explained",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "faṣṣalnāhu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُفَصِّلُ",
        "answer": "We explain",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "nufaṣṣilu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "174"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُفَصَّلَاتٍ",
        "answer": "manifest",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "mufaṣṣalātin",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَفْصِيلًا",
        "answer": "and explanation",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "watafṣīlan",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضَّلَكُمْ",
        "answer": "has preferred you",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "faḍḍalakum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَضْلٍ",
        "answer": "superiority",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "faḍlin",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلُوا",
        "answer": "they do",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "faʿalū",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلَ",
        "answer": "did",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "faʿala",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَعَلَ",
        "answer": "did",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "faʿala",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْقَهُونَ",
        "answer": "they understand",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yafqahūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَفَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "reflect",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yatafakkarūna",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَفَكَّرُوا",
        "answer": "they reflect",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "yatafakkarū",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُفْلِحُونَ",
        "answer": "succeed",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tuf'liḥūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْلِحُونَ",
        "answer": "(will be) the successful ones",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-muf'liḥūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُفْلِحُونَ",
        "answer": "the successful ones",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "l-muf'liḥūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفُلْكِ",
        "answer": "the ship",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-ful'ki",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَاقَ",
        "answer": "he recovered",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "afāqa",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقِهِمْ",
        "answer": "over them",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fawqihim",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَهُمْ",
        "answer": "over them",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "fawqahum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقَهُمْ",
        "answer": "above them",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "fawqahum",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفِيضُوا",
        "answer": "Pour",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "afīḍū",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكُمْ",
        "answer": "before you",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "qablikum",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "qabli",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before (us)",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلَ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "qabla",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَبِيلُهُ",
        "answer": "and his tribe",
        "pcklId": "286",
        "tlit": "waqabīluhu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقْتُلُونَنِي",
        "answer": "kill me",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yaqtulūnanī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَنُقَتِّلُ",
        "answer": "We will kill",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "sanuqattilu",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَتِّلُونَ",
        "answer": "they were killing",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "yuqattilūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَقْدِمُونَ",
        "answer": "seek to advance (it)",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yastaqdimūna",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرِئَ",
        "answer": "is recited",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "quri-a",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنُ",
        "answer": "the Quran",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-qur'ānu",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْرَبَا",
        "answer": "approach [both of you]",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "taqrabā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "اقْتَرَبَ",
        "answer": "come near ",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "iq'taraba",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرِيبٌ",
        "answer": "(is) near",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "qarībun",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُقَرَّبِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones who are near",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "l-muqarabīna",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِرَدَةً",
        "answer": "apes",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "qiradatan",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَقَرَّ",
        "answer": "it remains",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "is'taqarra",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْتَقَرٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) a dwelling place",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "mus'taqarrun",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَةٍ",
        "answer": "a city",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "qaryatin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your town",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "qaryatikum",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَتِنَا",
        "answer": "our city",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "qaryatinā",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرْيَةٍ",
        "answer": "a city",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "qaryatin",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) the cities",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-qurā",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) the cities",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-qurā",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) the cities",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-qurā",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(were) the cities ",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-qurā",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَرْيَةَ",
        "answer": "city",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-qaryata",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَرْيَةِ",
        "answer": "the town",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-qaryati",
        "frequency": "57",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْقِسْطِ",
        "answer": "justice",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "bil-qis'ṭi",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَاسَمَهُمَا",
        "answer": "And he swore (to) both of them",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "waqāsamahumā",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقْسَمْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you had sworn",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "aqsamtum",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقْصِرُونَ",
        "answer": "they cease",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yuq'ṣirūna",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "202"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُصُورًا",
        "answer": "palaces",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "quṣūran",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلَنَقُصَّنَّ",
        "answer": "Then surely We will narrate",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "falanaquṣṣanna",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُصُّونَ",
        "answer": "relating",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "yaquṣṣūna",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَقُصُّ",
        "answer": "We relate",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "naquṣṣu",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاقْصُصِ",
        "answer": "So relate",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "fa-uq'ṣuṣi",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَصَصَ",
        "answer": "the story",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "l-qaṣaṣa",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَطَعْنَا",
        "answer": "And We cut off",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "waqaṭaʿnā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأُقَطِّعَنَّ",
        "answer": "I will surely cut off",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "la-uqaṭṭiʿanna",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَطَّعْنَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "And We divided them",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "waqaṭṭaʿnāhumu",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَطَّعْنَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "And We divided them",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "waqaṭṭaʿnāhum",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "168"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَقْعُدَنَّ",
        "answer": "surely I will sit",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "la-aqʿudanna",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْعُدُوا",
        "answer": "sit",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "taqʿudū",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَانْقَلَبُوا",
        "answer": "and returned",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-inqalabū",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "119"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "qulūbihim",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبِ",
        "answer": "(the) hearts",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "qulūbi",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبٌ",
        "answer": "(are) hearts",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "qulūbun",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنْقَلِبُونَ",
        "answer": "(will) return",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "munqalibūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقَلَّتْ",
        "answer": "they have carried",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "aqallat",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "few",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "Little",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "Little",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقَمَرَ",
        "answer": "and the moon",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wal-qamara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقُمَّلَ",
        "answer": "and the lice",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wal-qumala",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَاهِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) subjugators",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "qāhirūna",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "383",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْنَا",
        "answer": "We said",
        "pcklId": "384",
        "tlit": "qul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "(Allah) said",
        "pcklId": "385",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "(Shaitaan) said",
        "pcklId": "386",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "(Allah) said",
        "pcklId": "387",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "(Shaitaan) said",
        "pcklId": "388",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "(Allah) said",
        "pcklId": "389",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "(Shaitaan) said",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "(Allah) said",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And he said",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقُلْ",
        "answer": "and [I] say",
        "pcklId": "393",
        "tlit": "wa-aqul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَا",
        "answer": "Both of them said",
        "pcklId": "394",
        "tlit": "qālā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "(Allah) said",
        "pcklId": "395",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "396",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "397",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "398",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "Do you say",
        "pcklId": "399",
        "tlit": "ataqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "400",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "401",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "402",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "403",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "you say",
        "pcklId": "404",
        "tlit": "taqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "405",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They say",
        "pcklId": "406",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He (will) say",
        "pcklId": "407",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَتْ",
        "answer": "(will) say",
        "pcklId": "408",
        "tlit": "qālat",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He (will) say",
        "pcklId": "409",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَتْ",
        "answer": "And (will) say",
        "pcklId": "410",
        "tlit": "waqālat",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they will say",
        "pcklId": "411",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They will say",
        "pcklId": "412",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they (will) say",
        "pcklId": "413",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "saying",
        "pcklId": "414",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They (will) say",
        "pcklId": "415",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُ",
        "answer": "will say",
        "pcklId": "416",
        "tlit": "yaqūlu",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَقَالَ",
        "answer": "and he said",
        "pcklId": "417",
        "tlit": "faqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "418",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "419",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "420",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "421",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "422",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "423",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "424",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "425",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "426",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "427",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "428",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and they said",
        "pcklId": "429",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "and he said",
        "pcklId": "430",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "431",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "432",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "433",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "434",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "435",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "436",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "and said",
        "pcklId": "437",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "and said",
        "pcklId": "438",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "439",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "104"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَقُولَ",
        "answer": "I say",
        "pcklId": "440",
        "tlit": "aqūla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "105"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "441",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "442",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "443",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "444",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "445",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "114"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "446",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "447",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "448",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "121"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "449",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "450",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "125"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "451",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "452",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "453",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "454",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "455",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "456",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they said",
        "pcklId": "457",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "132"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "458",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "459",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "460",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "461",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "140"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And said",
        "pcklId": "462",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "463",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "464",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "465",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "466",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "467",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "468",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "469",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "470",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "151"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he said",
        "pcklId": "471",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "He said",
        "pcklId": "472",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "473",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "it was said",
        "pcklId": "474",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "and say",
        "pcklId": "475",
        "tlit": "waqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "161"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "was said",
        "pcklId": "476",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَتْ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "477",
        "tlit": "qālat",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "478",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْنَا",
        "answer": "We said",
        "pcklId": "479",
        "tlit": "qul'nā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "and they say",
        "pcklId": "480",
        "tlit": "wayaqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "they will say",
        "pcklId": "481",
        "tlit": "yaqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They said",
        "pcklId": "482",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "you say",
        "pcklId": "483",
        "tlit": "taqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "you say",
        "pcklId": "484",
        "tlit": "taqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "485",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "486",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "487",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "488",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they say",
        "pcklId": "489",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "490",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْلًا",
        "answer": "word",
        "pcklId": "1645",
        "tlit": "qawlan",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْلِ",
        "answer": "[the] words",
        "pcklId": "1646",
        "tlit": "l-qawli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقِيمُوا",
        "answer": "and set",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "wa-aqīmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَقَامُوا",
        "answer": "and establish",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "wa-aqāmū",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for (the) people",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people ",
        "pcklId": "168",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "171",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "to his people",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "liqawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "80"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "(are) a people",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "qawmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) his people",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِنَا",
        "answer": "our people",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "qawminā",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "191",
        "tlit": "qawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمُ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "192",
        "tlit": "l-qawmu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "193",
        "tlit": "qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "194",
        "tlit": "qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَوْمَهُ",
        "answer": "and his people",
        "pcklId": "195",
        "tlit": "waqawmahu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "to his people",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "liqawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَوْمُهُ",
        "answer": "and his people",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "waqawmuhu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "200",
        "tlit": "qawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمٌ",
        "answer": "(are) a people",
        "pcklId": "201",
        "tlit": "qawmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "138"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِي",
        "answer": "my people",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "qawmī",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمَكَ",
        "answer": "your people",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "qawmaka",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمُ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "qawmu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "his people ",
        "pcklId": "205",
        "tlit": "qawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمَهُ",
        "answer": "(from) his people",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "qawmahu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) people",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمُهُ",
        "answer": "his people",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "qawmuhu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَوْمًا",
        "answer": "a people",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "qawman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "l-qawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمُ",
        "answer": "(are) the people",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "l-qawmu",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "to a people",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "506",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "507",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "508",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْتَقِيمَ",
        "answer": "the straight",
        "pcklId": "657",
        "tlit": "l-mus'taqīma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقُوَّةٍ",
        "answer": "with firmness",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "biquwwatin",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِقُوَّةٍ",
        "answer": "with strength",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "biquwwatin",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَائِلُونَ",
        "answer": "were sleeping at noon",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "qāilūna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَكَبَّرَ",
        "answer": "you be arrogant",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "tatakabbara",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَكَبَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "are arrogant",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yatakabbarūna",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَكْبَرُوا",
        "answer": "and (are) arrogant",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "wa-is'takbarū",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَكْبَرُوا",
        "answer": "and (were) arrogant",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wa-is'takbarū",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَسْتَكْبِرُونَ",
        "answer": "arrogant (about)",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "tastakbirūna",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَكْبَرُوا",
        "answer": "(who) were arrogant",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "is'takbarū",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَكْبَرُوا",
        "answer": "were arrogant",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "is'takbarū",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْتَكْبَرُوا",
        "answer": "were arrogant",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "is'takbarū",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاسْتَكْبَرُوا",
        "answer": "but they showed arrogance",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "fa-is'takbarū",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَكْبِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(do) they turn away in pride",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yastakbirūna",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "206"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَتَبْنَا",
        "answer": "And We ordained (laws)",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wakatabnā",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاكْتُبْ",
        "answer": "And ordain",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wa-uk'tub",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَأَكْتُبُهَا",
        "answer": "So I will ordain it",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "fasa-aktubuhā",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابٌ",
        "answer": "(This is) a Book",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "kitābun",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "160",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكِتَابٍ",
        "answer": "a Book",
        "pcklId": "161",
        "tlit": "bikitābin",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "162",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Book",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "to the Book",
        "pcklId": "164",
        "tlit": "bil-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "165",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكْتُوبًا",
        "answer": "written",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "maktūban",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَثَّرَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and He increased you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fakatharakum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَاسْتَكْثَرْتُ",
        "answer": "surely I could have multiplied",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "la-is'takthartu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "aktharahum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَكْثَرِهِمْ",
        "answer": "for most of them",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "li-aktharihim",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "aktharahum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "aktharahum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "131"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَ",
        "answer": "most",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "akthara",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَثِيرًا",
        "answer": "many",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "kathīran",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "deny",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "denies",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَذَّبُوهُ",
        "answer": "But they denied him",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "fakadhabūhu",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "they denied",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "they (had) denied",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبُوا",
        "answer": "denied",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "182"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذِبًا",
        "answer": "a lie",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "kadhiban",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذِبًا",
        "answer": "a lie",
        "pcklId": "203",
        "tlit": "kadhiban",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَاذِبِينَ",
        "answer": "the liars",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "l-kādhibīna",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَارِهِينَ",
        "answer": "(the) ones who hate (it)",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "kārihīna",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "earn",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "taksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "earn",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yaksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَشَفْتَ",
        "answer": "you remove",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "kashafta",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَشَفْنَا",
        "answer": "We removed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "kashafnā",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "426",
        "tlit": "kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "427",
        "tlit": "kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "428",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "429",
        "tlit": "kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "76"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(who are) disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "430",
        "tlit": "kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "431",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَلْبِ",
        "answer": "(of) the dog",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-kalbi",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُكَلِّفُ",
        "answer": "We burden",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nukallifu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "And for every",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "walikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكُلٍّ",
        "answer": "For each",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "likullin",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلًّا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "kullan",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "all (kinds)",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "on every",
        "pcklId": "84",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "[with] every",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "bikulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "112"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِكُلِّ",
        "answer": "for every",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "likulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "kulla",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "each",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلَّمَا",
        "answer": "Every time",
        "pcklId": "370",
        "tlit": "kullamā",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَلَّمَهُ",
        "answer": "and spoke to him",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wakallamahu",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَلِّمُهُمْ",
        "answer": "speak to them",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yukallimuhum",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبِكَلَامِي",
        "answer": "and with My words",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "wabikalāmī",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَلِمَاتِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Words",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "wakalimātihi",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَتُ",
        "answer": "(the) word",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "kalimatu",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَادُوا",
        "answer": "and were about to",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wakādū",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُنْ",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "340",
        "tlit": "yakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "341",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "342",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "were We",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُنْ",
        "answer": "he was",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "yakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُ",
        "answer": "it is",
        "pcklId": "346",
        "tlit": "yakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَكُونَا",
        "answer": "lest you both be",
        "pcklId": "347",
        "tlit": "fatakūnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَا",
        "answer": "you two become",
        "pcklId": "348",
        "tlit": "takūnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُونَا",
        "answer": "you two become",
        "pcklId": "349",
        "tlit": "takūnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "surely, we will be",
        "pcklId": "350",
        "tlit": "lanakūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "351",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "352",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "is",
        "pcklId": "353",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we were",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "(as) they used to",
        "pcklId": "358",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we used to",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "360",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "361",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "used to",
        "pcklId": "362",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "363",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "364",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "365",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "366",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتْ",
        "answer": "she was",
        "pcklId": "367",
        "tlit": "kānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "368",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "369",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you were",
        "pcklId": "370",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "371",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "(there) is",
        "pcklId": "372",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "87"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we are",
        "pcklId": "373",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُ",
        "answer": "it is",
        "pcklId": "374",
        "tlit": "yakūnu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "375",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "92"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "376",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "377",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "378",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "you have",
        "pcklId": "379",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتَ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "380",
        "tlit": "kunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "106"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we are",
        "pcklId": "381",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "113"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكُونَ",
        "answer": "we will be",
        "pcklId": "382",
        "tlit": "nakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "383",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and they were",
        "pcklId": "384",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "133"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and they were",
        "pcklId": "385",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "386",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "used to",
        "pcklId": "387",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "388",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "389",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "139"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنْ",
        "answer": "and be",
        "pcklId": "390",
        "tlit": "wakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and they were",
        "pcklId": "391",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "146"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "392",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَانُوا",
        "answer": "and they were",
        "pcklId": "393",
        "tlit": "wakānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "we will surely be",
        "pcklId": "394",
        "tlit": "lanakūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتْ",
        "answer": "were",
        "pcklId": "395",
        "tlit": "kānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "396",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "397",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "162"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَتْ",
        "answer": "was",
        "pcklId": "398",
        "tlit": "kānat",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "399",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "400",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُونُوا",
        "answer": "Be",
        "pcklId": "401",
        "tlit": "kūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنَّا",
        "answer": "we were",
        "pcklId": "402",
        "tlit": "kunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنَّا",
        "answer": "and we are",
        "pcklId": "403",
        "tlit": "wakunnā",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَانَ",
        "answer": "and he became",
        "pcklId": "404",
        "tlit": "fakāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "405",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "406",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونَ",
        "answer": "has",
        "pcklId": "407",
        "tlit": "yakūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُ",
        "answer": "I would",
        "pcklId": "408",
        "tlit": "kuntu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَنَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "surely we will be",
        "pcklId": "409",
        "tlit": "lanakūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you are",
        "pcklId": "410",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكُنْ",
        "answer": "be",
        "pcklId": "411",
        "tlit": "takun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَانَ",
        "answer": "(in) place",
        "pcklId": "1360",
        "tlit": "makāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَانَهُ",
        "answer": "in its place",
        "pcklId": "1361",
        "tlit": "makānahu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِيدُونِ",
        "answer": "scheme against me",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "kīdūni",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْدِي",
        "answer": "My plan",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "kaydī",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "183"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَيْفَ",
        "answer": "So how could",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "fakayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَيْفَ",
        "answer": "how",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "kayfa",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَيْلَ",
        "answer": "[the] measure",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-kayla",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَاسًا",
        "answer": "clothing",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "libāsan",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِبَاسُ",
        "answer": "But the clothing",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "walibāsu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِبَاسَهُمَا",
        "answer": "their clothing",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "libāsahumā",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُلْحِدُونَ",
        "answer": "deviate",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yul'ḥidūna",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْعَبُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) playing",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yalʿabūna",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "98"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَعِبًا",
        "answer": "and play",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "walaʿiban",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعَنَتْ",
        "answer": "it cursed",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "laʿanat",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَعْنَةُ",
        "answer": "(The) curse",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "laʿnatu",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَلْقَفُ",
        "answer": "swallow(ed)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "talqafu",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَلْقَىٰ",
        "answer": "So he threw",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "fa-alqā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "107"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُلْقِيَ",
        "answer": "you throw",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "tul'qiya",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْقُوا",
        "answer": "Throw",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "alqū",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْقَوْا",
        "answer": "they threw",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "alqaw",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْقِ",
        "answer": "Throw",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "alqi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُلْقِيَ",
        "answer": "And fell down",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "wa-ul'qiya",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "120"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَلْقَى",
        "answer": "And he cast down",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "wa-alqā",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "تِلْقَاءَ",
        "answer": "towards",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "til'qāa",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَاءَ",
        "answer": "(the) meeting",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "liqāa",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِقَاءِ",
        "answer": "and (the) meeting",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "waliqāi",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "147"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُلْقِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones to throw",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "l-mul'qīna",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "115"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْهَثْ",
        "answer": "he lolls out his tongue",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yalhath",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلْهَثْ",
        "answer": "he lolls out his tongue",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yalhath",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَهْوًا",
        "answer": "(as) an amusement",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "lahwan",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَلْوَاحِ",
        "answer": "the tablets ",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-alwāḥi",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَلْوَاحَ",
        "answer": "the tablets",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-alwāḥa",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "150"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَلْوَاحَ",
        "answer": "the tablets",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-alwāḥa",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "There is not",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْسَ",
        "answer": "There is not",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "laysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلَسْتُ",
        "answer": "Am I not",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "alastu",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْلَةً",
        "answer": "nights",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "laylatan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيْلَةً",
        "answer": "night(s)",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "laylatan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَتَاعٌ",
        "answer": "and livelihood",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "wamatāʿun",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَتِينٌ",
        "answer": "(is) firm",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "matīnun",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "183"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْلُهُ",
        "answer": "similar to it",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "mith'luhu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمَثَلُهُ",
        "answer": "So his example",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "famathaluhu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَمَثَلِ",
        "answer": "(is) like (the) example",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "kamathali",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلُ",
        "answer": "(is the) example",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "mathalu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلًا",
        "answer": "(as) an example",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "mathalan",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْثَالُكُمْ",
        "answer": "like you",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "amthālukum",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "194"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمُدُّونَهُمْ",
        "answer": "they plunge them",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yamuddūnahum",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "202"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَدَائِنِ",
        "answer": "the cities",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-madāini",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "111"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَدِينَةِ",
        "answer": "the city",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-madīnati",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "امْرَأَتَهُ",
        "answer": "his wife",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "im'ra-atahu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَمَرَّتْ",
        "answer": "and continues",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "famarrat",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمَسُّوهَا",
        "answer": "touch her",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "tamassūhā",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّ",
        "answer": "(had) touched",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "massa",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "95"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّنِيَ",
        "answer": "(could) have touched me",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "massaniya",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "touches them",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "massahum",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُمَسِّكُونَ",
        "answer": "hold fast",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yumassikūna",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "170"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْشُونَ",
        "answer": "(to) walk",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yamshūna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَمْطَرْنَا",
        "answer": "And We showered",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-amṭarnā",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَطَرًا",
        "answer": "a rain",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "maṭaran",
        "frequency": "15",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَرْتُمُوهُ",
        "answer": "you have plotted it",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "makartumūhu",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكْرَ",
        "answer": "(from the) plan",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "makra",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكْرَ",
        "answer": "(from the) plan",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "makra",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "99"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَمَكْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) surely a plot",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "lamakrun",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "123"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَّنَّاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We established you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "makkannākum",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَأَمْلَأَنَّ",
        "answer": "surely, I will fill",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "la-amla-anna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَأُ",
        "answer": "the chiefs",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "l-mala-u",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَأُ",
        "answer": "the chiefs",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-mala-u",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَأُ",
        "answer": "the chiefs",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-mala-u",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَأُ",
        "answer": "the chiefs",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-mala-u",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَأُ",
        "answer": "the chiefs",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-mala-u",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "90"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَلَئِهِ",
        "answer": "and his chiefs",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wamala-ihi",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَأُ",
        "answer": "the chiefs",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-mala-u",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "109"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَأُ",
        "answer": "the chiefs",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "l-mala-u",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمْلِكُ",
        "answer": "I have power",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "amliku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(is the) dominion",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمَلَائِكَةِ",
        "answer": "to the Angels",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "lil'malāikati",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلَكَيْنِ",
        "answer": "Angels",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "malakayni",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَلَكُوتِ",
        "answer": "(the) dominion",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "malakūti",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِلَّتِنَا",
        "answer": "our religion",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "millatinā",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "88"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِلَّتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your religion",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "millatikum",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُمْلِي",
        "answer": "And I will give respite",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wa-um'lī",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "183"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَعَكَ",
        "answer": "prevented you",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "manaʿaka",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَنَّ",
        "answer": "the manna",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-mana",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِهَادٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a bed",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "mihādun",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمُوتُونَ",
        "answer": "you will die",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "tamūtūna",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُمِيتُ",
        "answer": "and causes death",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "wayumītu",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَىٰ",
        "answer": "the dead",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "l-mawtā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَيِّتٍ",
        "answer": "dead",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "mayyitin",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَاءِ",
        "answer": "(some) water",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "l-māi",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَاءَ",
        "answer": "the water",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-māa",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْبَائِهَا",
        "answer": "their news",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "anbāihā",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "101"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَأَ",
        "answer": "(the) story",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "naba-a",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "175"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبِيٍّ",
        "answer": "Prophet",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "nabiyyin",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "94"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّبِيَّ",
        "answer": "the Prophet",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "l-nabiya",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّبِيِّ",
        "answer": "the Prophet",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "l-nabiyi",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَبَاتُهُ",
        "answer": "its vegetation",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "nabātuhu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَتَقْنَا",
        "answer": "We raised",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nataqnā",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالنُّجُومَ",
        "answer": "and the stars ",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wal-nujūma",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَجَّانَا",
        "answer": "saved us",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "najjānā",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْجَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "so We saved him",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "fa-anjaynāhu",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْجَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "So We saved him",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "fa-anjaynāhu",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْجَيْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "So We saved him",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "fa-anjaynāhu",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "83"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْجَيْنَاكُمْ",
        "answer": "We saved you",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "anjaynākum",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْجَيْنَا",
        "answer": "We saved",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "anjaynā",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَنْحِتُونَ",
        "answer": "and you carve out",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "watanḥitūna",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَادَاهُمَا",
        "answer": "And called them both",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "wanādāhumā",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُودُوا",
        "answer": "And they will be addressed",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wanūdū",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَادَىٰ",
        "answer": "And will call out",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wanādā",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَادَوْا",
        "answer": "And they will call out",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wanādaw",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَادَىٰ",
        "answer": "And (will) call out",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wanādā",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَادَىٰ",
        "answer": "And (will) call out",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "wanādā",
        "frequency": "53",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِتُنْذِرَ",
        "answer": "that you warn",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "litundhira",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُنْذِرَكُمْ",
        "answer": "that he may warn you",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "liyundhirakum",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُنْذِرَكُمْ",
        "answer": "that he may warn you",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "liyundhirakum",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِيرٌ",
        "answer": "a warner",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "nadhīrun",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "184"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَذِيرٌ",
        "answer": "a warner",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "nadhīrun",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْزِعُ",
        "answer": "stripping",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yanziʿu",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَزَعْنَا",
        "answer": "And We will remove",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wanazaʿnā",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَزَعَ",
        "answer": "And he drew out",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wanazaʿa",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْزَغَنَّكَ",
        "answer": "an evil suggestion comes to you",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yanzaghannaka",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزْغٌ",
        "answer": "[an evil suggestion]",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nazghun",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُنَزِّلْ",
        "answer": "He (has) sent down",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "yunazzil",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَّلَ",
        "answer": "(has been) sent down",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "nazzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَّلَ",
        "answer": "revealed",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "nazzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "revealed",
        "pcklId": "143",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "144",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We have sent down",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "then We send down",
        "pcklId": "146",
        "tlit": "fa-anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "has been sent down",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "and We sent down",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "wa-anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُسْخَتِهَا",
        "answer": "their inscription",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "nus'khatihā",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "النِّسَاءِ",
        "answer": "the women",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-nisāi",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "81"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِسَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their women",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "nisāahum",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِسَاءَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your women",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "nisāakum",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "141"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَنْسَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "We forget them",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "nansāhum",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسُوا",
        "answer": "they forgot",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "nasū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسُوهُ",
        "answer": "had forgotten it",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "nasūhu",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسُوا",
        "answer": "they forgot",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "nasū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصِيبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their portion",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "naṣībuhum",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْصِتُوا",
        "answer": "and pay attention",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-anṣitū",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "204"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْصَحُ",
        "answer": "and [I] advise",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-anṣaḥu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَصَحْتُ",
        "answer": "and [I] advised",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wanaṣaḥtu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَصَحْتُ",
        "answer": "and advised",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wanaṣaḥtu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاصِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the sincere advisors",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-nāṣiḥīna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاصِحٌ",
        "answer": "an adviser ",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "nāṣiḥun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاصِحِينَ",
        "answer": "the advisers",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "l-nāṣiḥīna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَصَرُوهُ",
        "answer": "and help him",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wanaṣarūhu",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْصُرُونَ",
        "answer": "can they help",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yanṣurūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "192"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْصُرُونَ",
        "answer": "can they help",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yanṣurūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصْرًا",
        "answer": "any help",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "naṣran",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "192"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصْرَكُمْ",
        "answer": "(to) help you",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "naṣrakum",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they wait",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "yanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْظُرْ",
        "answer": "So see",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "fa-unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "84"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَانْظُرُوا",
        "answer": "And see",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wa-unẓurū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْظُرْ",
        "answer": "So see",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "fa-unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "103"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَنْظُرَ",
        "answer": "then see",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "fayanẓura",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْظُرْ",
        "answer": "(that) I may look",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "anẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْظُرْ",
        "answer": "look",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "unẓur",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْظُرُوا",
        "answer": "they look",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yanẓurū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "185"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "looking",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْظِرْنِي",
        "answer": "Give me respite",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "anẓir'nī",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْظِرُونِ",
        "answer": "give me respite",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "tunẓirūni",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْتَظِرُوا",
        "answer": "Then wait",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "fa-intaẓirū",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاظِرِينَ",
        "answer": "for the observers",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "lilnnāẓirīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنْظَرِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones given respite",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "l-munẓarīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنْتَظِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the ones who wait",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "l-muntaẓirīna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَالْأَنْعَامِ",
        "answer": "(are) like cattle",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "kal-anʿāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "179"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَنَا",
        "answer": "ourselves",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "anfusanā",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسًا",
        "answer": "any soul",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "nafsan",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(to) themselves",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and themselves",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "wa-anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "177"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَفْسِي",
        "answer": "for myself",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "linafsī",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "a soul",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "192"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "197"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسِكَ",
        "answer": "yourself",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "nafsika",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "205"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْعًا",
        "answer": "(to) benefit",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "nafʿan",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "188"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَقْصٍ",
        "answer": "and a deficit",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wanaqṣin",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "130"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْقِمُ",
        "answer": "you take revenge",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "tanqimu",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَانْتَقَمْنَا",
        "answer": "So We took retribution",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "fa-intaqamnā",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْكُثُونَ",
        "answer": "broke (the word)",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yankuthūna",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "135"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَكِدًا",
        "answer": "(with) difficulty",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nakidan",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُنْكَرِ",
        "answer": "the wrong",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-munkari",
        "frequency": "37",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّهَارَ",
        "answer": "(with) the day",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "l-nahāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَهَاكُمَا",
        "answer": "forbid you both",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "nahākumā",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْهَكُمَا",
        "answer": "I forbid you both",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "anhakumā",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَنْهَاهُمْ",
        "answer": "and forbids them",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wayanhāhum",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْهَوْنَ",
        "answer": "forbade",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yanhawna",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "165"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُهُوا",
        "answer": "they were forbidden",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "nuhū",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "166"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَارٍ",
        "answer": "fire",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "nārin",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "النُّورَ",
        "answer": "the light",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "l-nūra",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسَ",
        "answer": "[the] people",
        "pcklId": "87",
        "tlit": "l-nāsa",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "88",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "116"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "144"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "mankind",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسِ",
        "answer": "(of) the people",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "l-nāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَاقَةُ",
        "answer": "(is) a she-camel",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "nāqatu",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاقَةَ",
        "answer": "the she-camel",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "l-nāqata",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَائِمُونَ",
        "answer": "(were) asleep",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "nāimūna",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "97"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنَالُهُمْ",
        "answer": "will reach them",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yanāluhum",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنَالُهُمُ",
        "answer": "(will) grant them",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yanāluhumu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيَنَالُهُمْ",
        "answer": "will reach them",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "sayanāluhum",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "152"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاهْبِطْ",
        "answer": "Then go down",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "fa-ih'biṭ",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْبِطُوا",
        "answer": "Get down",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ih'biṭū",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَىٰ",
        "answer": "He guided",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "hadā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَانَا",
        "answer": "guided us",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "hadānā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَانَا",
        "answer": "(had) guided us",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "hadānā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِ",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yahdi",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "guide them",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "yahdīhim",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "148"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَهْدِي",
        "answer": "and You guide",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "watahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدُونَ",
        "answer": "(which) guides",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yahdūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "159"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِ",
        "answer": "(is) guided",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yahdi",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدُونَ",
        "answer": "who guides",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yahdūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "181"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِنَهْتَدِيَ",
        "answer": "to receive guidance",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "linahtadiya",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَهْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "(be) guided",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "tahtadūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "158"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "as guidance",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدًى",
        "answer": "(was) guidance",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "hudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "154"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "the guidance",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "l-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "193"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "the guidance",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "l-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "198"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَهُدًى",
        "answer": "and guidance",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "tlit": "wahudan",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَادِيَ",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "293",
        "tlit": "hādiya",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهْتَدُونَ",
        "answer": "(are the) guided-ones",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "tlit": "muh'tadūna",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُهْتَدِي",
        "answer": "(is) the guided one",
        "pcklId": "315",
        "tlit": "l-muh'tadī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "178"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكْنَاهَا",
        "answer": "We destroyed it",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ahlaknāhā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُهْلِكَ",
        "answer": "will destroy",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "yuh'lika",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "129"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَهْلَكْتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "You (could) have destroyed them",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "ahlaktahum",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتُهْلِكُنَا",
        "answer": "Would You destroy us",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "atuh'likunā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَتُهْلِكُنَا",
        "answer": "So will You destroy us",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "afatuh'likunā",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "173"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُهْلِكُهُمْ",
        "answer": "(is going to) destroy them",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "muh'likuhum",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدْنَا",
        "answer": "we have turned",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "hud'nā",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُودًا",
        "answer": "Hud",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "hūdan",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَوَاهُ",
        "answer": "his (vain) desires",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "hawāhu",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "176"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيثَاقُ",
        "answer": "Covenant",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "mīthāqu",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجِدُ",
        "answer": "You (will) find",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "tajidu",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَدْنَا",
        "answer": "We found",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "wajadnā",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَدْنَا",
        "answer": "we found",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "wajadnā",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَدْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you found",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wajadttum",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَدْنَا",
        "answer": "We found",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "wajadnā",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَدْنَا",
        "answer": "We found",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "wajadnā",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "102"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجِدُونَهُ",
        "answer": "they find him",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yajidūnahu",
        "frequency": "107",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your faces",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "wujūhakum",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةٍ",
        "answer": "single",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatin",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "189"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحْدَهُ",
        "answer": "Alone",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "waḥdahu",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْحَيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We inspired",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wa-awḥaynā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "117"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْحَيْنَا",
        "answer": "And We inspired",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wa-awḥaynā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "160"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوحَىٰ",
        "answer": "is revealed",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yūḥā",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "203"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنَذَرَ",
        "answer": "and we forsake",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "wanadhara",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَذَرُوهَا",
        "answer": "So you leave her",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "fadharūhā",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَتَذَرُ",
        "answer": "Will you leave",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "atadharu",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَذَرَكَ",
        "answer": "and forsake you",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "wayadharaka",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "127"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَذَرُوا",
        "answer": "And leave",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wadharū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "180"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَذَرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "And He leaves them",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wayadharuhum",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "186"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرِثُونَ",
        "answer": "inherit",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "yarithūna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "100"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرِثُوا",
        "answer": "(who) inherited",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "warithū",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُورِثْتُمُوهَا",
        "answer": "you have been made to inherit it",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ūrith'tumūhā",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُورِثُهَا",
        "answer": "He causes to inherit it",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yūrithuhā",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْرَثْنَا",
        "answer": "And We made inheritors",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wa-awrathnā",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "137"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَقِ",
        "answer": "(the) leaves",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "waraqi",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُورِيَ",
        "answer": "was concealed",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wūriya",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوَارِي",
        "answer": "it covers",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "yuwārī",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوَازِينُهُ",
        "answer": "his scales",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "mawāzīnuhu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوَازِينُهُ",
        "answer": "his scales",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "mawāzīnuhu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْمِيزَانَ",
        "answer": "and the weight",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wal-mīzāna",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْوَزْنُ",
        "answer": "And the weighing",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "wal-waznu",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسِعَ",
        "answer": "Encompasses",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "wasiʿa",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسِعَتْ",
        "answer": "encompasses",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "wasiʿat",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُسْعَهَا",
        "answer": "(to) its capacity",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wus'ʿahā",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوَسْوَسَ",
        "answer": "Then whispered",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "fawaswasa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَضَعُ",
        "answer": "and he relieves",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wayaḍaʿu",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "157"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدَنَا",
        "answer": "(had) promised us",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "waʿadanā",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعَدَ",
        "answer": "(was) promised",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "waʿada",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعِدُنَا",
        "answer": "you promise us",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "taʿidunā",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعِدُنَا",
        "answer": "you promise us",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "taʿidunā",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "77"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوَاعَدْنَا",
        "answer": "And We appointed",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "wawāʿadnā",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُوعِدُونَ",
        "answer": "threatening",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "tūʿidūna",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "86"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعِظُونَ",
        "answer": "(do) you preach",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "taʿiẓūna",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْعِظَةً",
        "answer": "an instruction",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "mawʿiẓatan",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "145"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَوْفُوا",
        "answer": "So give full",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "fa-awfū",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "85"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَفَّوْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "(to) take them in death",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "yatawaffawnahum",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَوَفَّنَا",
        "answer": "and cause us to die",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "watawaffanā",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "126"
    },
    {
        "question": "مِيقَاتُ",
        "answer": "(the) set term",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "mīqātu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "142"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِمِيقَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "to Our appointed place",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "limīqātinā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "143"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِمِيقَاتِنَا",
        "answer": "for Our appointment",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "limīqātinā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِوَقْتِهَا",
        "answer": "its time",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "liwaqtihā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "187"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَعَ",
        "answer": "has fallen",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "waqaʿa",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوَقَعَ",
        "answer": "So was established",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "fawaqaʿa",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "118"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَعَ",
        "answer": "fell",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "waqaʿa",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "134"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاقِعٌ",
        "answer": "(would) fall",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wāqiʿun",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقَىٰ",
        "answer": "fears Allah",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "ittaqā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِتَتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "and that you may fear",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "walitattaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "you fear (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "tattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّقَوْا",
        "answer": "and feared Allah",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "wa-ittaqaw",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "96"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) righteous",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "yattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "156"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "become righteous",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "yattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "164"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "fear Allah",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "yattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "169"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "fear Allah",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "tattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "171"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقَوْا",
        "answer": "fear (Allah)",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "ittaqaw",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "201"
    },
    {
        "question": "التَّقْوَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] righteousness ",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "l-taqwā",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "(is) for the righteous",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "lil'muttaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "128"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَوَكَّلْنَا",
        "answer": "we put our trust",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "tawakkalnā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "89"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَلِجَ",
        "answer": "passes",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yalija",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَوَلَّىٰ",
        "answer": "So he turned away",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "fatawallā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "79"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَوَلَّىٰ",
        "answer": "So he turned away",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "fatawallā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "93"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَلَّى",
        "answer": "protects",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "yatawallā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "any allies",
        "pcklId": "174",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "friends",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "(as) allies",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيُّنَا",
        "answer": "(are) our Protector",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "waliyyunā",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "155"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلِيِّيَ",
        "answer": "my protector",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "waliyyiya",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "196"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "them",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَيْ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "yaday",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَهُ",
        "answer": "his hand",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yadahu",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "108"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your hands",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "aydiyakum",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "124"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "their hands",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "aydīhim",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "149"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْدٍ",
        "answer": "hands",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "aydin",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "195"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَمِّ",
        "answer": "the sea",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "l-yami",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "136"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيْمَانِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their right",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "aymānihim",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Day",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their day",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "yawmihim",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَيَّامٍ",
        "answer": "epochs",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ayyāmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "(of the) Day",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yawmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(the) Day",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "167"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "354",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَالْيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "So today",
        "pcklId": "355",
        "tlit": "fal-yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(The) Day",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) day",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "and (on the) day",
        "pcklId": "358",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "163"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "359",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "7",
        "ayah": "172"
    }
]; 
export default words;